<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sitenews on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/tags/sitenews/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Sitenews on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 06:56:52 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/tags/sitenews/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Website Reboot</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-big-website-reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 06:56:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-big-website-reboot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the new zzamboni.org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the other side</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/on-the-other-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/on-the-other-side/</guid>
      <description>About a year ago, Posterous was acquired by Twitter. A month ago, it was announced that it will be completely shut down by April 30th. I&amp;rsquo;ll spare you my rant about how the awesome customer service that characterized Posterous pre-acquisition completely disappeared after the acquisition :)
On a more practical note, Posterous&amp;rsquo; closing meant finding a new place to host my blogs. There are many options (you can find many of them described in the posthaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website redesign and unification</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/website-redesign-and-unification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 02:22:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/website-redesign-and-unification/</guid>
      <description>There are still some rough edges, but by far the redesign and unification of zzamboni.org is done. With the same design you can now find my blogs (hosted by posterous.com), my project pages (hosted in github.com project repositories) and some static pages (hosted in my personal github.com pages repository, this includes the root, About and Code pages, as well as the static copy of my old blog BrT, which is the only one that retains its original design).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated server and service setup</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/updated-server-and-service-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 14:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/updated-server-and-service-setup/</guid>
      <description>(a friend asked me about my online setup, and I wrote the text below. Then I realized it would also make an interesting blog post, and I just copied and pasted it, with minimal editing, into an email to posterous. This is why I love posterous, it makes posting so easy) 
For my setup, I have a hodgepodge of stuff all aggregated under the zzamboni.org domain. I wrote a blog post about my setup some time ago: http://blog.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>