<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Stevejobs on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>https://zzamboni.org/tags/stevejobs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Stevejobs on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 02:17:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zzamboni.org/tags/stevejobs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading on multiple media</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/reading-on-multiple-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 02:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/reading-on-multiple-media/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I finished reading Steve Jobs by Walter Isaacson. I thoroughly enjoyed it (I may post a longer review later on, but I really liked learning the &#34;behind the scenes&#34; of much of what I witnessed from the outside over so many years). 
With this book, for the first time, I decided to conduct an experiment. I got the book as an audiobook (from Audible, playing on my iPhone), as an ebook (using Kindle on my iPhone) and also the hardcover physical book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dennis M. Ritchie, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/dennis-m.-ritchie-r.i.p./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/dennis-m.-ritchie-r.i.p./</guid>
      <description>Dennis Ritchie passed away last weekend. He was one of the great minds in systems research and development, father of the C programming language, and one of the big contributors to Unix, both of which power the Mac on which I&#39;m typing this, the iPhone on my desk, the Windows machine I use at work, the servers on which this blog is hosted, and much of the infrastructure both you and I use to connect to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/steve-jobs-r.i.p./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:26:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/steve-jobs-r.i.p./</guid>
      <description>Farewell, Steve. Thank you for all you did for the computer industry, for design, for music, for telephony, and for so many other aspects of our lives. You will be missed.
  </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>