<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Facebook on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/tags/facebook/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Facebook on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 16:16:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/tags/facebook/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deleting my Facebook account</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2010-05-18-deleting-my-facebook-account-0/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 16:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2010-05-18-deleting-my-facebook-account-0/</guid>
      <description>Today I reactivated my Facebook account just to be able to delete it completely. If you find Facebook useful, you should at least be aware of its potential privacy issues, and tune your privacy settings to a level that you find comfortable. Here are some links where you can find more information: 
http://www.theregister.co.uk/2010/05/14/facebook_trust_dumb/ http://www.fastcompany.com/1624745/time-to-audit-your-facebook-privacy-settings http://www.fastcompany.com/1648478/online-privacy-check-yourself-before-you-w... 
Personally, I don&#39;t find Facebook useful enough to go through the hassle. My account has been deactivated for the last couple of weeks and I haven&#39;t missed it, so now it&#39;s time to permanently delete it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Privacy on Facebook and why I&#39;m dropping off</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2010-05-11-the-evolution-of-privacy-on-facebook-and-why/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 10:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2010-05-11-the-evolution-of-privacy-on-facebook-and-why/</guid>
      <description>via mattmckeon.com  This is a very good analysis, and is why my Facebook account is currently deactivated, and probably will be deleted. Contrary to Matt, I don&#39;t find Facebook very useful. Mostly it&#39;s served me to be found by people by whom I wasn&#39;t all that interested in being found, to see relatives&#39; photos (which I can also receive through other means), to be endlessly spammed by people playing Farmville and, most usefully, to contact people whose email addresses I don&#39;t have or can&#39;t bother to remember.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>