<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Howto on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>https://zzamboni.org/categories/howto/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Howto on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zzamboni.org/categories/howto/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast translation with Google Translator</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/fast-translation-with-google-translator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/fast-translation-with-google-translator/</guid>
      <description>via https://medium.com/@mrdoro/fast-translation-with-google-translator-and-mac-osx-817e32233b7a
 https://medium.com/@mrdoro/fast-translation-with-google-translator-and-mac-osx-817e32233b7a  Nice article about how to create a service to automatically translate selected text from any application. I use this all the time, I have a “German-to-English” service bound to Command-Alt-Ctrl-Shift-E, so I can just select text off the screen, press the shortcut, and a window with the translation will pop up. Very handy.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: use-package, a declarative configuration tool - Mastering Emacs</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/spotlight-use-package-a-declarative-configuration-tool-mastering-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/spotlight-use-package-a-declarative-configuration-tool-mastering-emacs/</guid>
      <description>via https://www.masteringemacs.org/article/spotlight-use-package-a-declarative-configuration-tool
 Have you ever heard of use-package? It’s a declarative way of expressing package configuration in Emacs but without the tears.  This looks amazingly useful. I need to start migrating my Emacs config to use-package ASAP.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving files between git repositories, preserving history</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/moving-files-between-git-repositories-preserving-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/moving-files-between-git-repositories-preserving-history/</guid>
      <description>I needed to copy a directory between two git repositories while preserving its history. I found some good instructions at http://gbayer.com/development/moving-files-from-one-git-repository-to-another-preserving-history/, which got me started, but I figured out a way to avoid having to move all the files into their directory again (lines 5-6 in Greg&amp;rsquo;s instructions) by reversing the filter to remove everything I don&amp;rsquo;t want instead of only including the directory I want. Here are the steps (the idea is the same as in Greg&amp;rsquo;s post, so please read that to get the explanation, I&amp;rsquo;m only listing the commands here for reference):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find all single-note tags in Evernote</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/find-all-single-note-tags-in-evernote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/find-all-single-note-tags-in-evernote/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working on cleaning up my Evernote, and noticed that I have a lot of tags assigned to a single note. I had successfully used Veritrope’s excellent Evernote empty tag remover applescript, so I made some small changes to write the attached script, which will find all single-note tags in your Evernote and list them in a new note, including links to each note. This makes it much easier to go through them and see which of those tags could be removed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to solve truncated docker output in Mac OS X using boot2docker</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-solve-truncated-docker-output-in-mac-os-x-using-boot2docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-solve-truncated-docker-output-in-mac-os-x-using-boot2docker/</guid>
      <description>If you are using docker on Mac OS X using boot2docker (http://docs.docker.io/installation/mac/), you may see truncated output from docker run, and also may have noticed that docker attach does not work properly, producing only some output and then exiting. This bug is documented here: https://github.com/boot2docker/boot2docker/issues/150, where I also found the following workaround. Documenting it here in case anyone finds it useful:
Instead of using the default value of DOCKER_HOST provided by boot2docker up, establish the docker connection through an ssh tunnel:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>