<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Tools on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/tags/tools/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Tools on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 19:41:00 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/tags/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>cf-cmd: A command-line tool for running CFEngine snippets</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cf-cmd-a-command-line-tool-for-running-cfengine-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 19:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cf-cmd-a-command-line-tool-for-running-cfengine-snippets/</guid>
      <description>After building the typical &#34;test bundle&#34; scaffolding in an editor for the hundredth time, I decided to do something about it. The result is the cf-cmd command. via blog.cf-learn.info  A little useful script I wrote for making it easier to test CFEngine code snippets. Follow the link to see the full details.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How important are the tools you use with GTD?</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-important-are-the-tools-you-use-with-gtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 09:24:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-important-are-the-tools-you-use-with-gtd/</guid>
      <description>via gtdtimes.com  Short video of David Allen talking about the importance of the GTD tools you choose. Conclusion: the most important thing is that you choose a tool you actually use, because the moment you stop putting your stuff in it, it will stop working.Timely for me as I rebuild my GTD toolbox and system this week.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know your tools </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/know-your-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 02:01:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/know-your-tools/</guid>
      <description>I recently had to copy a very large file (&amp;gt;4GB) from a remote Windows share to my Windows 7 machine, over a very finicky connection (frequently-failing VPN over a slow Internet connection). A GUI copy didn&#39;t work because the connection dropped frequently. I tried Free Download Manager, which was the recommended tool for the download, but surprisingly, it wasn&#39;t always able to restart the download after connectivity dropped.
Then a colleague pointed me to the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must-Have Windows Software (or Windows Programs that I use) - good coders code, great reuse</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/must-have-windows-software-or-windows-programs-that-i-use---good-coders-code-great-reuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 10:12:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/must-have-windows-software-or-windows-programs-that-i-use---good-coders-code-great-reuse/</guid>
      <description>I am not just a Linux enthusiast, I also happen to use Windows quite often. In fact, Windows is my primary desktop from which I connect to all the other boxes and do my work on. During the years of Windows usage, I have accumulated a list of must-have Windows programs that I wouldn’t be able to work without. Some of them are commercial, some are freeware, but that doesn’t matter.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>