<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Evernote on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>https://zzamboni.org/categories/evernote/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Evernote on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zzamboni.org/categories/evernote/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching for changes (Polling notifications) in Evernote</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/watching-for-changes-polling-notifications-in-evernote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/watching-for-changes-polling-notifications-in-evernote/</guid>
      <description>via https://dev.evernote.com/doc/articles/polling_notification.php
 Useful note about how to poll an Evernote account for new content. Also a test of web clipping with Enwrite. Polling If your app wants to know about changes in a user&#39;s Evernote account, you&#39;ll probably consider calling the NoteStore.findNotesMetadata function periodically to search for new notes. findNotes is incredibly powerful, but it&#39;s also expensive for our servers - we need to load the user&#39;s Lucene index, perform the search across all of their notes, hit the database to pull out the results, and send those results over the network to your app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find all single-note tags in Evernote</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/find-all-single-note-tags-in-evernote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/find-all-single-note-tags-in-evernote/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working on cleaning up my Evernote, and noticed that I have a lot of tags assigned to a single note. I had successfully used Veritrope’s excellent Evernote empty tag remover applescript, so I made some small changes to write the attached script, which will find all single-note tags in your Evernote and list them in a new note, including links to each note. This makes it much easier to go through them and see which of those tags could be removed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to turn off &#34;sort by relevance&#34; in Evernote 5.6.0 Beta</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-turn-off-sort-by-relevance-in-evernote-5-6-0-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-turn-off-sort-by-relevance-in-evernote-5-6-0-beta/</guid>
      <description> This was driving me crazy, but the fix is really easy (Source: https://discussion.evernote.com/topic/62259-evernote-for-mac-56-public-beta-1/?p=287015)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airmail tip: prevent &#34;Save to Evernote&#34; action from opening the created note</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/airmail-tip-prevent-save-to-evernote-action-from-opening-the-created-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/airmail-tip-prevent-save-to-evernote-action-from-opening-the-created-note/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been trying out Airmail as my main email app. It’s quite nice, I like the built-in integrations, particularly with Evernote. By default, when you use the “Save to Evernote” action, it saves the current message to Evernote and opens the newly-created note. I went spelunking into the Airmail application directory, and found the way to disable the note-opening. Follow these steps:   Quit Airmail (don’t know if this is necessary, but it can’t hurt) Open the Terminal app Run the following command in the terminal (all in a single line): sudo /Applications/Utilities/AppleScript\ Editor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>