<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Announcements on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/tags/announcements/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Announcements on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 08:30:32 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/tags/announcements/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>CFEngine talks at PICC&#39;12 conference</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2012-04-27-cfengine-talks-at-picc12-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 08:30:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2012-04-27-cfengine-talks-at-picc12-conference/</guid>
      <description>There will be several CFEngine-related classes and talks at the PICC&#39;12 conference (Professional IT Community Conference) on May 11-12th, in New Jersey. I will be talking about using CFEngine as part of your security infrastructure. My colleague Joe Netzel will be talking about migration from CFEngine 2 to CFEngine 3, so if you are using CF2 and have been considering (or dreading) the migration, make sure to come by! Aleksey Tsalolikhin will give an introductory class to CFEngine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning CFEngine 3 has been released</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2012-03-24-blog-learning-cfengine-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 01:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2012-03-24-blog-learning-cfengine-3/</guid>
      <description>  I am ecstatic to announce that the book is now officially released!
 via blog.cf-learn.info  I am so happy :-)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFEngine posts moving to cf-learn.info</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2012-01-04-cfengine-posts-moving-to-cf-learninfo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 13:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2012-01-04-cfengine-posts-moving-to-cf-learninfo/</guid>
      <description>I have been blogging about CFEngine here for a while (it&#39;s my most frequent tag). As of now, I&#39;m starting to post all CFEngine-related posts to http://blog.cf-learn.info/, which is part of the web site for my book &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34;. In this way, I intend to group all CFEngine-related content over there. I will still cross-post relevant things here, but if you want to stay fully up to date on my CFEngine writings, please subscribe over there as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New website for &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-12-15-new-website-for-learning-cfengine-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 02:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-12-15-new-website-for-learning-cfengine-3/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m happy to announce that the website for my book is now live at http://cf-learn.info/. 
In this website you will find:  General information about the book.  A discussion forum for any type of questions, feedback or suggestions about the book.  Downloadable code examples from the book, plus (over time) many other new examples.  List of Errata, and access to the Errata system at O&#39;Reilly  A blog devoted to the book and to CFEngine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Introduction to CFEngine 3 Nova&#34; webinar</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-25-introduction-to-cfengine-3-nova-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 22:53:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-25-introduction-to-cfengine-3-nova-webinar/</guid>
      <description>A new version of CFEngine 3 Nova was released today, and to go with it, there will be a free webinar called &#34;Introduction to CFEngine 3 Nova&#34; on November 2nd. It will be presented by one of the members of the core CFEngine team, and it will be a great opportunity to learn more about the new and improved capabilities in this release. If you are interested in CFEngine and maybe thinking of going the commercial route, or you need more information to decide, make sure to attend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New job, new book</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-19-new-job-new-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:21:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-19-new-job-new-book/</guid>
      <description>Today I have two big announcements to make.
First, as of this week I have a new job, I am now working with CFEngine AS, the company that develops and maintains cfengine. As you know if you read my blog, I am a big fan of cfengine. It is a mature and able tool that provides extreme flexibility and power to system administrators. The company is full of energy and with very interesting projects to make cfengine even better and more popular than it is today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>