<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Literateprogramming on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/tags/literateprogramming/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Literateprogramming on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 13:31:00 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/tags/literateprogramming/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>My Hammerspoon Configuration, With Commentary</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-hammerspoon-configuration-with-commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 13:31:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-hammerspoon-configuration-with-commentary/</guid>
      <description>Last update: June 3, 2018
In my ongoing series of literate config files, I present to you my Hammerspoon configuration file. You can see the generated file at https://github.com/zzamboni/dot-hammerspoon/blob/master/init.lua. As usual, this is just a snapshot at the time shown above, you can see the current version of my configuration in GitHub.
General variables and configuration Global log level. Per-spoon log level can be configured in each Install:andUse block below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Emacs Configuration, With Commentary</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-emacs-configuration-with-commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 20:14:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-emacs-configuration-with-commentary/</guid>
      <description>Last update: June 3, 2018
I have enjoyed slowly converting my configuration files to literate programming style style using org-mode in Emacs. I previously posted my Elvish configuration, and now it&amp;rsquo;s the turn of my Emacs configuration file. The text below is included directly from my init.org file. Please note that the text below is a snapshot as the file stands as of the date shown above, but it is always evolving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Elvish Configuration With Commentary</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-elvish-configuration-with-commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 20:21:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-elvish-configuration-with-commentary/</guid>
      <description>Last update: June 3, 2018
In this blog post I will walk you through my current Elvish configuration file, with running commentary about the different sections.
This is also my first blog post written using org-mode, which I have started using for writing and documenting my code, using literate programming. The content below is included unmodified from my rc.org file (as of the date shown above), from which the rc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>