<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Config on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>https://zzamboni.org/tags/config/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Config on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:25:00 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://zzamboni.org/tags/config/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Using and writing completions in Elvish</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/using-and-writing-completions-in-elvish/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jun 2018 20:25:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/using-and-writing-completions-in-elvish/</guid>
      <description>Like other Unix shells, Elvish has advanced command-argument completion capabilities. In this article I will explore the existing completions, and show you how you can create your own (and contribute them back to the community).
Using existing completions There is a growing body of shell completions that you can simply load and use.
Elvish has a still-small but growing collection of completions that have been created by its users. These are a few that I know of (let me know if you know others!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beautifying Org Mode in Emacs</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/beautifying-org-mode-in-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 22:45:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/beautifying-org-mode-in-emacs/</guid>
      <description>Over the last few months, I have used org-mode more and more for writing and programming in Emacs. I love its flexibility and power, and it is the first literate programming tool which &amp;ldquo;feels right&amp;rdquo;, and I have been able to stick with it for a longer period of time than in my previous attempts.
Recently I started thinking about how I could make my editing environment more visually appealing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Hammerspoon Configuration, With Commentary</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/my-hammerspoon-configuration-with-commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2018 13:31:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/my-hammerspoon-configuration-with-commentary/</guid>
      <description>Last update: July 26, 2018
In my ongoing series of literate config files, I present to you my Hammerspoon configuration file. You can see the generated file at https://github.com/zzamboni/dot-hammerspoon/blob/master/init.lua. As usual, this is just a snapshot at the time shown above, you can see the current version of my configuration in GitHub.
General variables and configuration Global log level. Per-spoon log level can be configured in each Install:andUse block below.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Emacs Configuration, With Commentary</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/my-emacs-configuration-with-commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Dec 2017 20:14:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/my-emacs-configuration-with-commentary/</guid>
      <description>Last update: July 26, 2018
I have enjoyed slowly converting my configuration files to literate programming style style using org-mode in Emacs. I previously posted my Elvish configuration, and now it&amp;rsquo;s the turn of my Emacs configuration file. The text below is included directly from my init.org file. Please note that the text below is a snapshot as the file stands as of the date shown above, but it is always evolving.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bang-Bang (!!, !$) Shell Shortcuts in Elvish</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/bang-bang---shell-shortcuts-in-elvish/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2017 22:15:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/bang-bang---shell-shortcuts-in-elvish/</guid>
      <description>(Updated on March 19th, 2018 to use the new Elvish Package Manager)
The bash shortcuts (maybe older? I&amp;rsquo;m not sure in which shell these originated) for &amp;ldquo;last command&amp;rdquo; (!!) and &amp;ldquo;last argument of last command&amp;rdquo; (!$) are, for me at least, among the most strongly imprinted in my muscle memory, and I use them all the time. Although these shortcuts are not available in Elvish by default, they are easy to implement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Elvish Configuration With Commentary</title>
      <link>https://zzamboni.org/post/my-elvish-configuration-with-commentary/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2017 20:21:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://zzamboni.org/post/my-elvish-configuration-with-commentary/</guid>
      <description>Last update: July 26, 2018
In this blog post I will walk you through my current Elvish configuration file, with running commentary about the different sections.
This is also my first blog post written using org-mode, which I have started using for writing and documenting my code, using literate programming. The content below is included unmodified from my rc.org file (as of the date shown above), from which the rc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>