<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 22:37:17 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Elvish, an awesome Unix shell</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/elvish-an-awesome-unix-shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2017 17:09:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/elvish-an-awesome-unix-shell/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m always on the lookout for new toys, particularly if they make my work more productive or enjoyable. For a couple of months now I have been using a new Unix shell called Elvish as my default login shell on macOS, and I love it. It’s a young project but very usable and with some very nice features.
Here are a few of the things I like about it:
 The Elvish language is clean and powerful, with clear syntax.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Limited Time Promotion! 50% off &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/limited-time-sale-learncf3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 13:45:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/limited-time-sale-learncf3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;For one week only, until September 20th, 2017, you can buy the new
ebook release of &amp;ldquo;Learning CFEngine 3&amp;rdquo; on Amazon at 50% off its list
price, US$4.98 instead of the regular US$9.99.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing the Outlook-to-OmniFocus Script</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fixing-outlook-to-omnifocus-script/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Sep 2017 21:11:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fixing-outlook-to-omnifocus-script/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Here&amp;rsquo;s how to fix the breakage caused by one of the recent updates to
Microsoft Outlook in the Outlook-to-OmniFocus AppleScript included
with my SendToOmniFocus spoon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Spoons in Hammerspoon</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/using-spoons-in-hammerspoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 20:17:55 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/using-spoons-in-hammerspoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;In this second article about Hammerspoon, we look into &lt;em&gt;Spoons&lt;/em&gt;,
modules written in Lua which can be easily installed and loaded into
Hammerspoon to provide ready-to-use functionality. Spoons provide a
predefined API to configure and use them. They are also a good way to
share your own work with other users.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Release of &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-release-of-learning-cfengine-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 11:16:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-release-of-learning-cfengine-3/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A new release of my book &amp;ldquo;Learning CFEngine 3&amp;rdquo; is now available!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hosting a Ghost Blog in GitHub - the easier way</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/hosting-a-ghost-blog-in-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/hosting-a-ghost-blog-in-github/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;When I was planning the reboot of my website, I seriously considered using Ghost. It has a very nice UI, beautiful and usable theme out of the box, and a very active community. Eventually I decided to use Hugo, but in the process discovered that it is possible to host a statically-generated Ghost website using GitHub Pages.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting Started With Hammerspoon</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/getting-started-with-hammerspoon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Aug 2017 16:34:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/getting-started-with-hammerspoon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the first installment of a series of posts about Hammerspoon,
a staggeringly powerful automation utility which gives you an amazing
degree of control over your Mac, allowing you to automate and control
almost anything. In the word of Hammerspoon&amp;rsquo;s motto: &lt;em&gt;Making the
runtime, funtime&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Big Website Reboot</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-big-website-reboot/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2017 06:56:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-big-website-reboot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to the new zzamboni.org.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning CFEngine 3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/book/cfengine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 17:56:58 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/book/cfengine/</guid>
      <description>&lt;iframe style=&#34;width:120px;height:240px;float:right&#34; marginwidth=&#34;0&#34; marginheight=&#34;0&#34; scrolling=&#34;no&#34; frameborder=&#34;0&#34; src=&#34;//ws-na.amazon-adsystem.com/widgets/q?ServiceVersion=20070822&amp;OneJS=1&amp;Operation=GetAdHtml&amp;MarketPlace=US&amp;source=ac&amp;ref=qf_sp_asin_til&amp;ad_type=product_link&amp;tracking_id=zzamboni-20&amp;marketplace=amazon&amp;region=US&amp;placement=B07562BSWG&amp;asins=B07562BSWG&amp;linkId=8d7eb3010d7a790fe0dd80c1f44fbea0&amp;show_border=true&amp;link_opens_in_new_window=true&amp;price_color=333333&amp;title_color=0066c0&amp;bg_color=ffffff&#34;&gt;
&lt;/iframe&gt;


&lt;p&gt;I am the author of &amp;ldquo;Learning CFEngine 3&amp;rdquo;, the best book for learning &lt;a href=&#34;http://cfengine.com/&#34;&gt;CFEngine&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The book has its own webpage at &lt;a href=&#34;http://cf-learn.info&#34;&gt;http://cf-learn.info&lt;/a&gt;, please visit it for more information.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can buy the book from Amazon by clicking the link on the right.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grabcartoons</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/code/grabcartoons/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2017 17:25:50 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/code/grabcartoons/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;GrabCartoons is a comic-summarizing utility. It is modular, and it is
very easy to write modules for new comics.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fast translation with Google Translator</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fast-translation-with-google-translator/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fast-translation-with-google-translator/</guid>
      <description>via https://medium.com/@mrdoro/fast-translation-with-google-translator-and-mac-osx-817e32233b7a
 https://medium.com/@mrdoro/fast-translation-with-google-translator-and-mac-osx-817e32233b7a  Nice article about how to create a service to automatically translate selected text from any application. I use this all the time, I have a “German-to-English” service bound to Command-Alt-Ctrl-Shift-E, so I can just select text off the screen, press the shortcut, and a window with the translation will pop up. Very handy.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Enwrite featured in onethingwell.org!</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/enwrite-featured-in-onethingwell-org/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/enwrite-featured-in-onethingwell-org/</guid>
      <description>via http://onethingwell.org/post/140035085825/enwrite
 I’m so proud (and of course posting this from Evernote using the web clipper) 😃 Enwrite ⇒ Evernote-powered statically-generated blogs and websites.
Post from the Evernote application on any device, use the web clipper, or post by email. Enwrite will pick up the new content and post it automatically…
 As well as turning new notes into weblog posts, you can use Enwrite to convert the contents of existing Evernote notebooks into a static site, using search terms and tags to select notes for publication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spotlight: use-package, a declarative configuration tool - Mastering Emacs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/spotlight-use-package-a-declarative-configuration-tool-mastering-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Feb 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/spotlight-use-package-a-declarative-configuration-tool-mastering-emacs/</guid>
      <description>via https://www.masteringemacs.org/article/spotlight-use-package-a-declarative-configuration-tool
 Have you ever heard of use-package? It’s a declarative way of expressing package configuration in Emacs but without the tears.  This looks amazingly useful. I need to start migrating my Emacs config to use-package ASAP.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clicking on the MacBook Pro is entirely artificial</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/clicking-on-the-macbook-pro-is-entirely-artificial/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Oct 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/clicking-on-the-macbook-pro-is-entirely-artificial/</guid>
      <description>via http://sixcolors.com/post/2015/10/apple-magic-trackpad-2-review/
 This is probably old news for most, but it still blew my mind: only now I realized that the clicking feeling and sound on my MacBook Pro’s trackpad is artificially generated. I did the experiment of turning on “Silent clicking” and turning off “Force click and haptic feedback” on the trackpad preferences panel and, indeed, the clicking is gone. Wow (/ht @jsnell)  To aid in the process, the Magic Trackpad apparently even generates its own artificial clicking noise (as the Force Touch trackpads in the MacBook and MacBook Pro do).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4-year-old’s first aerobatic flight</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/4-year-old-s-first-aerobatic-flight/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/4-year-old-s-first-aerobatic-flight/</guid>
      <description>via http://kottke.org/15/06/airplane-aerobatics-are-hilarious
What a fun video. Encore!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using Multiple SSH Keys with Github</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/using-multiple-ssh-keys-with-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/using-multiple-ssh-keys-with-github/</guid>
      <description>via http://www.freshblurbs.com/blog/2013/06/22/github-multiple-ssh-keys.html#tldr
 Since Github doesn&#39;t allow us to reuse an SSH Key, the only sane solution is to jump through some hoops and generate + use multiple keys on the server itself. Let&#39;s look at some effective approaches of doing that.  Short version: define multiple hosts in the SSH config file for each repository, which use different SSH keys, then you can assign different deploy keys to each repo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Emacs problems with the fish shell</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fixing-emacs-problems-with-the-fish-shell/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fixing-emacs-problems-with-the-fish-shell/</guid>
      <description>I started getting errors from the TRAMP Emacs package because I was using fish as my default shell, and it does not recognize certain standard syntax elements (such as &amp;amp;&amp;amp; to separate commands), and Emacs runs subcommands under the default shell. I fixed this by:
 Changing my account&#39;s default shell back to `/bin/bash` Changing my Terminal.app preferences to run `/usr/local/bin/fish` when a shell opens, instead of the default login shell:  Log out and back in to have everything reloaded properly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The log: The lifeblood of your data pipeline - O&#39;Reilly Radar</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-log-the-lifeblood-of-your-data-pipeline-o-reilly-radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-log-the-lifeblood-of-your-data-pipeline-o-reilly-radar/</guid>
      <description>via http://radar.oreilly.com/2015/04/the-log-the-lifeblood-of-your-data-pipeline.html
 Interesting article. I hadn’t heard of Fluentd, looks useful.   The old paradigm — machines to humans, and the new — machines to machines. Image courtesy of Kiyoto Tamura.   Over the last decade, the primary consumer of log data shifted from humans to machines.  Software engineers still read logs, especially when their software behaves in an unexpected manner. However, in terms of “bytes processed,” humans account for a tiny fraction of the total consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Whisky - Matt Gemmell</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/whisky-matt-gemmell/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/whisky-matt-gemmell/</guid>
      <description>via http://mattgemmell.com/whisky/
Nice essay.But then, finally, with one last branch hacked from your way, you set eyes upon it, and stand there. Silent and still. Perhaps you raise a hand, feeling time-worn stone beneath your fingertips. A dream, finally made solid. You’ve come so far, and now, at last, you’re here. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moving files between git repositories, preserving history</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/moving-files-between-git-repositories-preserving-history/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/moving-files-between-git-repositories-preserving-history/</guid>
      <description>I needed to copy a directory between two git repositories while preserving its history. I found some good instructions at http://gbayer.com/development/moving-files-from-one-git-repository-to-another-preserving-history/, which got me started, but I figured out a way to avoid having to move all the files into their directory again (lines 5-6 in Greg&amp;rsquo;s instructions) by reversing the filter to remove everything I don&amp;rsquo;t want instead of only including the directory I want. Here are the steps (the idea is the same as in Greg&amp;rsquo;s post, so please read that to get the explanation, I&amp;rsquo;m only listing the commands here for reference):</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The First Apple Homepage</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-first-apple-homepage/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-first-apple-homepage/</guid>
      <description>via http://kfury.com/the-first-apple-homepage
 Looks positively old-fashioned now, but the memories! I don’t remember this particular page, but I do remember compiling and using Mosaic as my first web browser on an old DECstation 5000, my first Unix workstation.    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three levels of GIT config</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/three-levels-of-git-config/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/three-levels-of-git-config/</guid>
      <description>via http://www.codinginahurry.com/2011/02/05/three-levels-of-git-config/
 Very nice explanation, via coding in a hurry There are 3 levels of git config; project, global and system.    project: Project configs are only available for the current project and stored in .git/config in the project&#39;s directory. global: Global configs are available for all projects for the current user and stored in ~/.gitconfig. system: System configs are available for all the users/projects and stored in /etc/gitconfig.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watching for changes (Polling notifications) in Evernote</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/watching-for-changes-polling-notifications-in-evernote/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/watching-for-changes-polling-notifications-in-evernote/</guid>
      <description>via https://dev.evernote.com/doc/articles/polling_notification.php
 Useful note about how to poll an Evernote account for new content. Also a test of web clipping with Enwrite. Polling If your app wants to know about changes in a user&#39;s Evernote account, you&#39;ll probably consider calling the NoteStore.findNotesMetadata function periodically to search for new notes. findNotes is incredibly powerful, but it&#39;s also expensive for our servers - we need to load the user&#39;s Lucene index, perform the search across all of their notes, hit the database to pull out the results, and send those results over the network to your app.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to create a new KVM VM using command line tools</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-create-a-new-kvm-vm-using-command-line-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-create-a-new-kvm-vm-using-command-line-tools/</guid>
      <description> I got tired of clicking through virt-manager to create new VMs, so I found the command needed to create one from the command line (thanks https://acidborg.wordpress.com/2010/02/18/how-to-create-virtual-machines-using-kvm-kernel-based-virtual-machine/):  virt-install --name=hostname --arch=x86_64 --vcpus=2 --ram=4096 --os-type=linux --os-variant=rhel7 --hvm --connect=qemu:///system --network bridge:br-fabric --cdrom=/var/lib/libvirt/images/CentOS-7.0-1406-x86_64-Minimal.iso --disk path=/var/lib/libvirt/images/hostname.img,size=32 --accelerate --vnc   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Find all single-note tags in Evernote</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/find-all-single-note-tags-in-evernote/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Jan 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/find-all-single-note-tags-in-evernote/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been working on cleaning up my Evernote, and noticed that I have a lot of tags assigned to a single note. I had successfully used Veritrope’s excellent Evernote empty tag remover applescript, so I made some small changes to write the attached script, which will find all single-note tags in your Evernote and list them in a new note, including links to each note. This makes it much easier to go through them and see which of those tags could be removed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to turn off &#34;sort by relevance&#34; in Evernote 5.6.0 Beta</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-turn-off-sort-by-relevance-in-evernote-5-6-0-beta/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-turn-off-sort-by-relevance-in-evernote-5-6-0-beta/</guid>
      <description> This was driving me crazy, but the fix is really easy (Source: https://discussion.evernote.com/topic/62259-evernote-for-mac-56-public-beta-1/?p=287015)    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>You’re probably using the wrong dictionary</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/you-re-probably-using-the-wrong-dictionary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Jul 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/you-re-probably-using-the-wrong-dictionary/</guid>
      <description> You’re probably using the wrong dictionary « the jsomers.net blog  &amp;gt; Which is to say you get a feeling about English that Calvin once got with his pet tiger on a day of fresh-fallen snow: “It’s a magical world, Hobbes. Let’s go exploring!”  Very nice article. I ended up using the package from this page, which has slightly-better formatting in my opinion.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mac keyboard shortcuts by Matt Gemmell</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/mac-keyboard-shortcuts-by-matt-gemmell/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/mac-keyboard-shortcuts-by-matt-gemmell/</guid>
      <description>Another great article by Matt Gemmell. I knew most of them, but learned a few things. The golden part for me were the third-party utilities, in particular Shortcat, which I didn’t know and is amazing:  &amp;gt; It’s basically Spotlight but for all visible controls and objects on the screen: it’s type-to-select for *everything you can see*.   The whole article is worth a read.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to solve truncated docker output in Mac OS X using boot2docker</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-solve-truncated-docker-output-in-mac-os-x-using-boot2docker/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-solve-truncated-docker-output-in-mac-os-x-using-boot2docker/</guid>
      <description>If you are using docker on Mac OS X using boot2docker (http://docs.docker.io/installation/mac/), you may see truncated output from docker run, and also may have noticed that docker attach does not work properly, producing only some output and then exiting. This bug is documented here: https://github.com/boot2docker/boot2docker/issues/150, where I also found the following workaround. Documenting it here in case anyone finds it useful:
Instead of using the default value of DOCKER_HOST provided by boot2docker up, establish the docker connection through an ssh tunnel:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Working from home - Matt Gemmell</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/working-from-home-matt-gemmell/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/working-from-home-matt-gemmell/</guid>
      <description>Great article.  I’ve been working from home full-time for more than seven years, and running my own business for the same amount of time. Many of us at least have the opportunity to occasionally work from home, and I daresay that many people would like the chance to do so permanently. It’s not just as straightforward as pulling out a laptop in the living room, though. Working from home has a number of difficulties and challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Airmail tip: prevent &#34;Save to Evernote&#34; action from opening the created note</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/airmail-tip-prevent-save-to-evernote-action-from-opening-the-created-note/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/airmail-tip-prevent-save-to-evernote-action-from-opening-the-created-note/</guid>
      <description>I’ve been trying out Airmail as my main email app. It’s quite nice, I like the built-in integrations, particularly with Evernote. By default, when you use the “Save to Evernote” action, it saves the current message to Evernote and opens the newly-created note. I went spelunking into the Airmail application directory, and found the way to disable the note-opening. Follow these steps:   Quit Airmail (don’t know if this is necessary, but it can’t hurt) Open the Terminal app Run the following command in the terminal (all in a single line): sudo /Applications/Utilities/AppleScript\ Editor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to stop com.apple.dock.extra from &#34;using significant energy&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-stop-com-apple-dock-extra-from-using-significant-energy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-stop-com-apple-dock-extra-from-using-significant-energy/</guid>
      <description>I’d been having for some time a problem with `com.apple.dock.extra` appearing in the “Apps using significant energy” section of the battery menu. I just learned the solution (from http://forums.macrumors.com/showthread.php?t=1651662): remove BusyCal 1.6 (I upgraded to BusyCal 2, but left the old version around in case I had to go back to it). After removing it and restarting the Dock, the problem stopped.  From the same thread, it seems the problem was caused by BusyCal’s “animate transitions” preference.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Explanation of temperature scales</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/explanation-of-temperature-scales/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/explanation-of-temperature-scales/</guid>
      <description>Interesting explanation, via http://ralfmaximus.tumblr.com/post/73635353732/spinningyarns-doctorbee-xwidep-scales   This is because Fahrenheit is based on a brine scale and the human body. The scale is basically how cold does it have to be to freeze saltwater (zero Fahrenheit) to what temperature is the human body (100-ish Fahrenheit, although now we know that’s not exactly accurate). Fahrenheit was designed around humans.  Celsius and Kelvin are designed around the natural world.  Celsius is a scale based on water.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing markdown support</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/testing-markdown-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/testing-markdown-support/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m giving an Ignite talk for the first time at DevOps days Paris. It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting format: a 5-minute talk with 20 auto-advancing slides, every 15 seconds. I found How to Give a great Ignite Talk by Scott Berkun very useful, including the accompanying video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Top 5 Recommended Google Font Combinations</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/top-5-recommended-google-font-combinations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Dec 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/top-5-recommended-google-font-combinations/</guid>
      <description>via http://www.studiopress.com/design/google-font-combinations.htm
Nice suggestions.   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Honest trailer: Man of Steel</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/honest-trailer-man-of-steel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/honest-trailer-man-of-steel/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ellen on password security</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ellen-on-password-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2013 14:46:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ellen-on-password-security/</guid>
      <description>Hilarious - Ellen on the &amp;ldquo;Internet Password Minder&amp;rdquo;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignite talks</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ignite-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Apr 2013 12:13:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ignite-talks/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m giving an Ignite talk for the first time at DevOps days Paris. It&amp;rsquo;s an interesting format: a 5-minute talk with 20 auto-advancing slides, every 15 seconds. I found How to Give a great Ignite Talk by Scott Berkun very useful, including the accompanying video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On the other side</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/on-the-other-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Mar 2013 15:57:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/on-the-other-side/</guid>
      <description>About a year ago, Posterous was acquired by Twitter. A month ago, it was announced that it will be completely shut down by April 30th. I&amp;rsquo;ll spare you my rant about how the awesome customer service that characterized Posterous pre-acquisition completely disappeared after the acquisition :)
On a more practical note, Posterous&amp;rsquo; closing meant finding a new place to host my blogs. There are many options (you can find many of them described in the posthaven.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HowTo: Changing the available display formats for Evernote&#39;s &#34;Insert Date&#34; command</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/howto-changing-the-available-display-formats-for-evernotes-insert-date-command/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Nov 2012 23:00:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/howto-changing-the-available-display-formats-for-evernotes-insert-date-command/</guid>
      <description>Evernote introduced some time ago an &#34;Insert Date&#34; keyboard shortcut, which is very handy. However, the options for the format of the inserted date seemed limited (only four options). I finally learned how this works, and how to change it on the Mac. The formats offered are those that are configured in the &#34;Languages &amp;amp; Text&#34; preferences panel. If you go to &#34;Region&#34; and then click the &#34;Customize button&#34; in the Dates part of the panel, you will see and be able to customize the formats for short, medium, long and full date representations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Included in the #LinuxCon registration packet: a skateboard#</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/included-in-the-#linuxcon-registration-packet-a-skateboard%23/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2012 23:46:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/included-in-the-#linuxcon-registration-packet-a-skateboard%23/</guid>
      <description>
  Included in the #LinuxCon registration packet: a skateboard# via twittelator  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Letters of Note: Regarding your dam complaint</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/letters-of-note-regarding-your-dam-complaint/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2012 12:59:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/letters-of-note-regarding-your-dam-complaint/</guid>
      <description>I would like to challenge you to attempt to emulate their dam project any dam time and/or any dam place you choose. I believe I can safely state there is no dam way you could ever match their dam skills, their dam resourcefulness, their dam ingenuity, their dam persistence, their dam determination and/or their dam work ethic. via lettersofnote.com  Amazing letter - read the whole thing, it&#39;s incredibly funny.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The CFEngine agent, as drawn by my 6-year-old daughter :)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-cfengine-agent-as-drawn-by-my-6-year-old-daughter-/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jul 2012 15:30:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-cfengine-agent-as-drawn-by-my-6-year-old-daughter-/</guid>
      <description>
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When a Dragon mated the space station /ht @BadAstronomer</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/when-a-dragon-mated-the-space-station-/ht-badastronomer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 May 2012 11:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/when-a-dragon-mated-the-space-station-/ht-badastronomer/</guid>
      <description>At 16:02 UTC, Friday, May 25, 2012, the SpaceX Dragon officially became the first privately-owned commercial spacecraft to be captured by and berthed at the International Space Station. It is (if I’ve done the math correctly) the 114th spacecraft to dock with ISS, including the missions sent up to build the station. It is the first privately-owned commercial spacecraft in history to do so.
 via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Amazing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFEngine talks at PICC&#39;12 conference</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine-talks-at-picc12-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Apr 2012 08:30:32 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine-talks-at-picc12-conference/</guid>
      <description>There will be several CFEngine-related classes and talks at the PICC&#39;12 conference (Professional IT Community Conference) on May 11-12th, in New Jersey. I will be talking about using CFEngine as part of your security infrastructure. My colleague Joe Netzel will be talking about migration from CFEngine 2 to CFEngine 3, so if you are using CF2 and have been considering (or dreading) the migration, make sure to come by! Aleksey Tsalolikhin will give an introductory class to CFEngine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Earth Day, from 40,000 km up | Bad Astronomy | Discover Magazine</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/earth-day-from-40000-km-up--bad-astronomy--discover-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Apr 2012 20:13:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/earth-day-from-40000-km-up--bad-astronomy--discover-magazine/</guid>
      <description>

 via blogs.discovermagazine.com  This video is simply amazing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publishing with iBooks Author - O&#39;Reilly Media</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/publishing-with-ibooks-author-oreilly-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Apr 2012 17:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/publishing-with-ibooks-author-oreilly-media/</guid>
      <description>     via shop.oreilly.com  Free e-book from O&#39;Reilly.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bezos Expeditions | F-1 Engine Recovery</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/bezos-expeditions--f-1-engine-recovery/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 23:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/bezos-expeditions--f-1-engine-recovery/</guid>
      <description>Photo credit: NASA I&#39;m excited to report that, using state-of-the-art deep sea sonar, the team has found the Apollo 11 engines lying 14,000 feet below the surface, and we&#39;re making plans to attempt to raise one or more of them from the ocean floor.
 via bezosexpeditions.com  Those are BIG engines. Would be awesome to recover them.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub: Instantly Beautiful Project Pages</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/github-instantly-beautiful-project-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2012 23:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/github-instantly-beautiful-project-pages/</guid>
      <description>Ever pushed a new project to GitHub and wished you had the time or talent to make a beautiful page for it? Stop wishing. We&#39;re proud to present the new GitHub Page Generator. via github.com  Very nice new feature.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Purdue at Night</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/purdue-at-night/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Mar 2012 00:01:14 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/purdue-at-night/</guid>
      <description>I am at Purdue to give a CFEngine talk and visit some old colleagues, here are some photos I took during a night walk right after checking into my hotel. I graduated in 2001, and the last time I visited was almost 10 years ago. Time really flies, there are many new things in campus (including the shiny new Computer Science Building, which I had never seen), but so many others remain unchanged.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learning CFEngine 3 has been released</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/learning-cfengine-3-has-been-released/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2012 01:23:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/learning-cfengine-3-has-been-released/</guid>
      <description>  I am ecstatic to announce that the book is now officially released!
 via blog.cf-learn.info  I am so happy :-)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Analytics put to a good cause</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/analytics-put-to-a-good-cause/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Mar 2012 17:05:57 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/analytics-put-to-a-good-cause/</guid>
      <description>Well, here&#39;s a good use of web analytics. From LinkedIn:
 Seeing a lot of daily digests piling up?
Diego, we noticed you haven&#39;t visited  lately. To help keep your email tidy, we&#39;ve switched you from daily emails to weekly digests from this group - we hope this suits you better!  Actually useful. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A dog&#39;s gotta do what a dog&#39;s gotta doo doo | The Sun |News</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-dogs-gotta-do-what-a-dogs-gotta-doo-doo--the-sun-news/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Mar 2012 17:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-dogs-gotta-do-what-a-dogs-gotta-doo-doo--the-sun-news/</guid>
      <description> via thesun.co.uk  Poor dog, but hilarious video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>github/gitignore</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/github/gitignore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Mar 2012 09:10:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/github/gitignore/</guid>
      <description>A collection of useful .gitignore templates via github.com  Useful resource.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Heart Stop Beating | Jeremiah Zagar on Vimeo</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/heart-stop-beating--jeremiah-zagar-on-vimeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 13:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/heart-stop-beating--jeremiah-zagar-on-vimeo/</guid>
      <description> via vimeo.com  Amazing - a continuous-flow artificial heart. You can live without a pulse.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Six-Legged Giant Finds Secret Hideaway, Hides For 80 Years : Krulwich Wonders... : NPR</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/six-legged-giant-finds-secret-hideaway-hides-for-80-years--krulwich-wonders...--npr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Mar 2012 00:11:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/six-legged-giant-finds-secret-hideaway-hides-for-80-years--krulwich-wonders...--npr/</guid>
      <description>Rod Morris/www.rodmorris.co.nz 
   The story is simple: A bunch of black rats almost wiped out a bunch of gigantic bugs on a little island far, far away from most of us. A few dedicated scientists, passionate about biological diversity, risked their lives to keep the bugs going. For the bugs to get their homes and their future back doesn&#39;t depend on scientists anymore. They&#39;ve done their job. Now it&#39;s up to the folks on Lord Howe Island.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A punto de comenzar. Torneo de #TaeKwonDo en Querétaro</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-punto-de-comenzar.-torneo-de-#taekwondo-en-quer%C3%A9taro/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2012 09:50:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-punto-de-comenzar.-torneo-de-#taekwondo-en-quer%C3%A9taro/</guid>
      <description>
  via Tweetbot for iPhone  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Fantastic Flying Books of Mr. Morris Lessmore (2011) - YouTube</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-fantastic-flying-books-of-mr.-morris-lessmore-2011---youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2012 23:50:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-fantastic-flying-books-of-mr.-morris-lessmore-2011---youtube/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Beautiful.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Lists of Note: Henry Miller&#39;s 11 Commandments</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/lists-of-note-henry-millers-11-commandments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2012 09:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/lists-of-note-henry-millers-11-commandments/</guid>
      <description>COMMANDMENTS
 Work on one thing at a time until finished. Start no more new books, add no more new material to &#34;Black Spring.&#34; Don&#39;t be nervous. Work calmly, joyously, recklessly on whatever is in hand. Work according to Program and not according to mood. Stop at the appointed time! When you can&#39;t create you can work. Cement a little every day, rather than add new fertilizers. Keep human! See people, go places, drink if you feel like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Our new popcorn machine :)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/our-new-popcorn-machine-/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2012 17:15:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/our-new-popcorn-machine-/</guid>
      <description>
  via Tweetbot for iPhone  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing &#34;message:&#34; protocol handler from Sparrow back to Mail.app</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/changing-message-protocol-handler-from-sparrow-back-to-mail.app/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 09:54:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/changing-message-protocol-handler-from-sparrow-back-to-mail.app/</guid>
      <description>After using Sparrow for a while, I have decided to switch back to Mail.app. However, even after setting my default email client to Mail.app, all my message: links (for example, from messages dragged from Mail.app into Things) were opening in Sparrow.
After some experimentation, I figured out what happened: I switched the default email client from Sparrow to Mail using Mail&#39;s preference panel: 
    
Apparently this switches the application for the mailto: protocol, but not for message:, nor for .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to remove a subproject/submodule to a git-svn repository</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-remove-a-subproject/submodule-to-a-git-svn-repository/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2012 03:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-remove-a-subproject/submodule-to-a-git-svn-repository/</guid>
      <description>To sum up, you delete the offending directory and then run something to the effect of  git filter-branch --index-filter \
&#39;git rm --cached --ignore-unmatch path/to/the/formerly/misbehaving/module&#39;
 via ignoredbydinosaurs.com  I accidentally added another git repository to a git-svn repository, which makes it die when trying to push the changes. This technique helped me fix it. Documenting mostly so I remember when it happens again sometime.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>nwdiag - simple network-diagram image generators — blockdiag 1.0 documentation</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/nwdiag---simple-network-diagram-image-generators--blockdiag-1.0-documentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2012 22:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/nwdiag---simple-network-diagram-image-generators--blockdiag-1.0-documentation/</guid>
      <description>nwdiag generates network-diagram image file from .diag file. .diag file is similar to DOT file (graphviz’s).
You can get diagrams like this.
 blockdiag.com via @saintaardvark  Very useful, like Graphviz but specifically for network diagrams. You can probably obtain the same result with Graphviz with the appropriate amount of dot magic, but nwdiag makes this very easy. Other useful graph types in sister projects: http://blockdiag.com/en/index.html
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Harbin International Ice and Snow Festival 2012 - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/harbin-international-ice-and-snow-festival-2012---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2012 01:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/harbin-international-ice-and-snow-festival-2012---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  A-ma-zing. All made from ice.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Joy of Books - YouTube</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-joy-of-books---youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 19:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-joy-of-books---youtube/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Wow, the amount of work that went into making this makes me dizzy.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Every Presentation Ever</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/every-presentation-ever/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2012 15:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/every-presentation-ever/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Communicate Better.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I broke my Zagg Smartbuds :(</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/i-broke-my-zagg-smartbuds-/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 20:36:33 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/i-broke-my-zagg-smartbuds-/</guid>
      <description>The cable caught on my knee while working out and snapped off the microphone unit :( Hope to get it repaired or replaced, I love these headphones. 
   

 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How One Bit of Stupidity Could Have Brought Down a Multi-Million Dollar Media Company | Peter Shankman</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-one-bit-of-stupidity-could-have-brought-down-a-multi-million-dollar-media-companypeter-shankman/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2012 13:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-one-bit-of-stupidity-could-have-brought-down-a-multi-million-dollar-media-companypeter-shankman/</guid>
      <description>the man sitting next to me was reading proprietary information, information that could be very, very damaging to this company if in the wrong hands, and he couldn’t have cared less about it via shankman.com  Fascinating, scary story. It&#39;s amazing the things people do in airplanes (particularly on their laptops/iPads/phones) as if no one was watching them. Situational awareness is very important.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Restart Page - Free unlimited rebooting experience from vintage operating systems</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-restart-page---free-unlimited-rebooting-experience-from-vintage-operating-systems/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Jan 2012 00:29:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-restart-page---free-unlimited-rebooting-experience-from-vintage-operating-systems/</guid>
      <description> via daring fireball.net  Awesome. So many memories.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Geographic Photography Contest Winners: 2011 - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/national-geographic-photography-contest-winners-2011---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Jan 2012 11:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/national-geographic-photography-contest-winners-2011---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  It&#39;s been a while since a linked to a Big Picture set, but this one deserves it. They are all beautiful photographs.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Font Squirrel</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/font-squirrel/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 20:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/font-squirrel/</guid>
      <description>We know how hard it is to find quality freeware that is licensed for commercial work. We&#39;ve done the hard work, hand-selecting these typefaces and presenting them in an easy-to-use format. via fontsquirrel.com  Lots of nice, free fonts.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fraser Speirs - Blog - Misconceptions About iOS Multitasking</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fraser-speirs---blog---misconceptions-about-iosmultitasking/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 15:27:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fraser-speirs---blog---misconceptions-about-iosmultitasking/</guid>
      <description>Let me wrap this up by giving you a quick summary:
 If someone tells you that all the apps in the multitasking bar are running, using up memory or sucking power, they are wrong. When you hit the home button, an app moves from Active to Background and quickly to the Suspended state where it no longer uses CPU time or drains power. An app may request an additional 10 minutes of Background running to complete a big task before becoming Suspended.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CFEngine posts moving to cf-learn.info</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine-posts-moving-to-cf-learn.info/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2012 13:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine-posts-moving-to-cf-learn.info/</guid>
      <description>I have been blogging about CFEngine here for a while (it&#39;s my most frequent tag). As of now, I&#39;m starting to post all CFEngine-related posts to http://blog.cf-learn.info/, which is part of the web site for my book &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34;. In this way, I intend to group all CFEngine-related content over there. I will still cross-post relevant things here, but if you want to stay fully up to date on my CFEngine writings, please subscribe over there as well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pile still left to process in my year-start #GTD review. Trying to start the yr with a clean slate/desk. The wine helps</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pile-still-left-to-process-in-my-year-start-#gtd-review.-trying-to-start-the-yr-with-a-clean-slate/desk.-the-wine-helps/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Jan 2012 14:35:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pile-still-left-to-process-in-my-year-start-#gtd-review.-trying-to-start-the-yr-with-a-clean-slate/desk.-the-wine-helps/</guid>
      <description>
  via Tweetbot for iPhone  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cf-cmd: A command-line tool for running CFEngine snippets</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cf-cmd-a-command-line-tool-for-running-cfengine-snippets/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Dec 2011 19:41:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cf-cmd-a-command-line-tool-for-running-cfengine-snippets/</guid>
      <description>After building the typical &#34;test bundle&#34; scaffolding in an editor for the hundredth time, I decided to do something about it. The result is the cf-cmd command. via blog.cf-learn.info  A little useful script I wrote for making it easier to test CFEngine code snippets. Follow the link to see the full details.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>15 Years Ago Today</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/15-years-ago-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2011 01:49:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/15-years-ago-today/</guid>
      <description>15 Years Ago Today  Apple acquired NeXT. Not a bad move.
  via daringfireball.net  Not a bad move indeed. I loved NeXT computers and NEXTSTEP, and I&#39;m happy every time I see its legacy on my Mac.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reading on multiple media</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/reading-on-multiple-media/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2011 02:17:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/reading-on-multiple-media/</guid>
      <description>A couple of days ago I finished reading Steve Jobs by Walter Isaacson. I thoroughly enjoyed it (I may post a longer review later on, but I really liked learning the &#34;behind the scenes&#34; of much of what I witnessed from the outside over so many years). 
With this book, for the first time, I decided to conduct an experiment. I got the book as an audiobook (from Audible, playing on my iPhone), as an ebook (using Kindle on my iPhone) and also the hardcover physical book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New website for &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-website-for-learning-cfengine-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 02:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-website-for-learning-cfengine-3/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m happy to announce that the website for my book is now live at http://cf-learn.info/. 
In this website you will find:  General information about the book.  A discussion forum for any type of questions, feedback or suggestions about the book.  Downloadable code examples from the book, plus (over time) many other new examples.  List of Errata, and access to the Errata system at O&#39;Reilly  A blog devoted to the book and to CFEngine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix journal in an HFS&#43; file system</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fix-journal-in-an-hfs--file-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2011 00:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fix-journal-in-an-hfs--file-system/</guid>
      <description>Yesterday my external Western Digital disk (which I use for Time Machine, among other things) stopped mounting automatically when I plug it in. This may *cough*definitely*cough*have something to do with me unmounting it forcefully while it was doing a backup, since I was in a hurry.
Disk Utility reported everything was OK with the disk, but it still failed to mount. Upon poking a bit deeper, I found these messages in the logs:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34; Early Release now available -use AUTHD to get 40-50% off</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/learning-cfengine-3early-release-now-available--use-authd-to-get-40-50-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2011 15:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/learning-cfengine-3early-release-now-available--use-authd-to-get-40-50-off/</guid>
      <description>Learning CFEngine 3 Automated system administration for sites of any size  By Diego Zamboni    via shop.oreilly.com  My upcoming book &#34;Learning CFEngine 3&#34; is now available as an Early Release, which includes (for now) the first four chapters of the book. You can use the code AUTHD to get 40% off the print book, or 50% off the ebook version.
Go get yours!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Linux kernel panic on train station screen at Boston airport </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/linux-kernel-panic-on-train-station-screen-at-boston-airport/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2011 16:56:19 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/linux-kernel-panic-on-train-station-screen-at-boston-airport/</guid>
      <description>
  via Tweetbot for iPhone  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WANT: Topbrewer - Scanomat</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/want-topbrewer---scanomat/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Dec 2011 23:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/want-topbrewer---scanomat/</guid>
      <description>  via scanomat.com  I remember joking in grad school that we should&#39;ve had coffee-on-tap so we didn&#39;t need to walk all the way down to the kitchen. Seems my dream has come true. I want one of these.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Remapping Mac modifier keys on Emacs 23.3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/remapping-mac-modifier-keys-on-emacs-23.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Nov 2011 01:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/remapping-mac-modifier-keys-on-emacs-23.3/</guid>
      <description>I just switched from Carbon Emacs (which is old Emacs 22.x) to Emacs for OS X Modified on my Mac (which is a Cocoa app, and Emacs 23.3).

One of the unwelcome changes was that the Emacs &#39;Meta&#39; modifier is now by default mapped to the Option key and not Command as before. But this gave me the opportunity to learn how to map the Mac keyboard modifier keys arbitrarily.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Security in the Third Wave of IT Engineering&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/security-in-the-third-wave-of-it-engineering/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 17:56:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/security-in-the-third-wave-of-it-engineering/</guid>
      <description>Today I gave a presentation at UNAM&#39;s 2011 Computer Security Conference in Mexico City. Below you will find my presentation (done using prezi.com, follow this link if you can&#39;t see it below). You can also get the PDF version.
  Security in the Third Wave of IT Engineering on Prezi
   Related blog posts from cfengine.com:
CFEngine - The Third Wave of Configuration Management
CFEngine, SysAdmin 3.0 and the Third Wave of IT Engineering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Congreso de Seguridad en Computo 2011</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/congreso-de-seguridad-en-computo-2011/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2011 10:53:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/congreso-de-seguridad-en-computo-2011/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m attending UNAM&#39;s computer security conference, giving a talk as well. Some photos from the event (will be updated throughout the day)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>JAW DROPPING Space Station time lapse! | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/jaw-dropping-space-station-time-lapse--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Nov 2011 16:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/jaw-dropping-space-station-time-lapse--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>
 via Bad Astronomy  Amazing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symphony of Science: Onward to the Edge</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/symphony-of-science-onward-to-the-edge/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2011 00:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/symphony-of-science-onward-to-the-edge/</guid>
      <description> via feedproxy.google.com  Very nice video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New Volcano Pictures: &#34;Monstrous&#34; Eruption in the Congo</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-volcano-pictures-monstrous-eruption-in-the-congo/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 19:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-volcano-pictures-monstrous-eruption-in-the-congo/</guid>
      <description>  Nyamulagira, which generally erupts every two years, rumbled to life at 8:06 p.m via news.nationalgeographic.com  Must be an amazing sight.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FoxTrot&#39;s homage to Steve Jobs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/foxtrots-homage-to-steve-jobs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 18:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/foxtrots-homage-to-steve-jobs/</guid>
      <description>  via gocomics.com    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cinema Stunt by Carlsberg | THEINSPIRATION.COM l THIS IS WH▲T INSPIRES US</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cinema-stunt-by-carlsberg--theinspiration.com-l-this-is-wht-inspires-us/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2011 11:35:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cinema-stunt-by-carlsberg--theinspiration.com-l-this-is-wht-inspires-us/</guid>
      <description> via theinspiration.com  One time on a plane from Brussels to Chicago, I was trying to make space in the overhead for my backpack, by moving a large bag with a flowery stamped design. A large tattooed, biker-type guy across the aisle says to me: &#34;please be careful, I&#39;m transporting a china set in there&#34;.
Never judge people by their appearance :)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quadrocopters</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/quadrocopters/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2011 21:54:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/quadrocopters/</guid>
      <description>Quadrocopters are really getting popular for research, and for a reason - they are seriously cool.  Arms / grippers have already been used on them:

 They can also do ball jugling:

 Have precise movement control:

 And do mapping:  
Tip of the rotor blade to Axel Tanner for sending me these. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Video: A Murmuration of Starlings - Alexis Madrigal - Technology - The Atlantic</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/video-a-murmuration-of-starlings---alexis-madrigal---technology---the-atlantic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2011 17:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/video-a-murmuration-of-starlings---alexis-madrigal---technology---the-atlantic/</guid>
      <description>via theatlantic.com  Wow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2011 Pan American Games - Alan Taylor - In Focus - The Atlantic</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-pan-american-games---alan-taylor---in-focus---the-atlantic/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Nov 2011 00:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-pan-american-games---alan-taylor---in-focus---the-atlantic/</guid>
      <description>  via theatlantic.com  Nice photo set from the Panamerican Games.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>All the apps on my iPhone</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/all-the-apps-on-my-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Oct 2011 10:19:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/all-the-apps-on-my-iphone/</guid>
      <description>I’m doing some cleanup and reorganization, and captured my current app setup as a reference point. Here they are.
Quick note: The first screen is my most-used apps (some are going out now, like 2Do which I&#39;ve never liked too much, but was the best way to sync tasks with Outlook, which I&#39;m no longer forced using). Second screen is all my folders. Third and fourth screens are my girls&#39; screens, with the games they use when they borrow my phone.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Invention on &#39;30 Rock&#39; 02/03/11</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-new-invention-on-30-rock-02/03/11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Oct 2011 11:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-new-invention-on-30-rock-02/03/11/</guid>
      <description>via daringfireball.net  Voice recognition is hard :)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What&#39;s New in CFEngine 3: Making System Administration Even More Powerful - O&#39;Reilly Radar</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/whats-new-in-cfengine-3-making-system-administration-even-more-powerful---oreilly-radar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Oct 2011 16:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/whats-new-in-cfengine-3-making-system-administration-even-more-powerful---oreilly-radar/</guid>
      <description>CFEngine is both the oldest and the newest of the popular tools for automating site administration. Mark Burgess invented it as a free software project in 1993, and years later, as deployments in the field outgrew its original design he gave it a complete rethink and developed the powerful concept of promise theory to make it modular and maintainable.via radar.oreilly.com  I contributed to this article by Andy Oram on CFEngine 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GitHub Secrets</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/github-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2011 01:06:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/github-secrets/</guid>
      <description>Let&#39;s talk about some of those secret features you may not know about.
 via github.com  Nice article about some lesser-known GitHub features.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Introduction to CFEngine 3 Nova&#34; webinar</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/introduction-to-cfengine-3-nova-webinar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Oct 2011 22:53:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/introduction-to-cfengine-3-nova-webinar/</guid>
      <description>A new version of CFEngine 3 Nova was released today, and to go with it, there will be a free webinar called &#34;Introduction to CFEngine 3 Nova&#34; on November 2nd. It will be presented by one of the members of the core CFEngine team, and it will be a great opportunity to learn more about the new and improved capabilities in this release. If you are interested in CFEngine and maybe thinking of going the commercial route, or you need more information to decide, make sure to attend!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dennis Ritchie, 70, Dies, Programming Trailblazer - NYTimes.com</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/dennis-ritchie-70-dies-programming-trailblazer---nytimes.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Oct 2011 13:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/dennis-ritchie-70-dies-programming-trailblazer---nytimes.com/</guid>
      <description>The tools that Dennis built — and their direct descendants — run pretty much everything today. —Brian Kernighan
via nytimes.com  Nice article about Dennis Ritchie.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Michael Winslow gets the Led out</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/michael-winslow-gets-the-led-out/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 23:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/michael-winslow-gets-the-led-out/</guid>
      <description>
 via kottke.org  WHOA, WHERE THE HELL DID THAT GUITAR NOISE COME FROM??!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CNET UK Presents: History of the iPhone, dedicated to the memory of Steve Jobs on Vimeo</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cnet-uk-presents-history-of-the-iphone-dedicated-to-the-memory-of-steve-jobs-on-vimeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 15:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cnet-uk-presents-history-of-the-iphone-dedicated-to-the-memory-of-steve-jobs-on-vimeo/</guid>
      <description> via vimeo.com  Nice video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New job, new book</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-job-new-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Oct 2011 00:21:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/new-job-new-book/</guid>
      <description>Today I have two big announcements to make.
First, as of this week I have a new job, I am now working with CFEngine AS, the company that develops and maintains cfengine. As you know if you read my blog, I am a big fan of cfengine. It is a mature and able tool that provides extreme flexibility and power to system administrators. The company is full of energy and with very interesting projects to make cfengine even better and more popular than it is today.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Llama Song</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-llama-song/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 15:51:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-llama-song/</guid>
      <description> via albinoblacksheep.com  And now for an oldie but most definitely a goodie - the Llama Song! (click on the link to see it in its full forever-repeating glory)
Llama Llama Duck.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quantum locking demo</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/quantum-locking-demo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2011 08:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/quantum-locking-demo/</guid>
      <description> via jasonadriaan.com  Amazing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dennis M. Ritchie, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/dennis-m.-ritchie-r.i.p./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/dennis-m.-ritchie-r.i.p./</guid>
      <description>Dennis Ritchie passed away last weekend. He was one of the great minds in systems research and development, father of the C programming language, and one of the big contributors to Unix, both of which power the Mac on which I&#39;m typing this, the iPhone on my desk, the Windows machine I use at work, the servers on which this blog is hosted, and much of the infrastructure both you and I use to connect to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/steve-jobs-r.i.p./</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:26:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/steve-jobs-r.i.p./</guid>
      <description>Farewell, Steve. Thank you for all you did for the computer industry, for design, for music, for telephony, and for so many other aspects of our lives. You will be missed.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Schultz, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/gene-schultz-r.i.p./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 23:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/gene-schultz-r.i.p./</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I learned through Spaf that Gene Schultz had had a severe accident and was hospitalized. Later we learned that the accident was apparently caused by an earlier stroke that went unrecognized. Yesterday, October 2nd, during the afternoon, Gene passed away.

I met Gene about 15 years ago while I was a grad student at Purdue. I met him initially at a couple of conferences, and later while he was visiting Purdue for some time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>RC Helicopter Flight Test Gone Bad</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/rc-helicopter-flight-test-gone-bad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2011 07:40:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/rc-helicopter-flight-test-gone-bad/</guid>
      <description>on youtube.com via web-heads. There&#39;s probably a recall on these.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientists Reconstruct Brains’ Visions Into Digital Video In Historic Experiment | Gizmodo</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/scientists-reconstruct-brains-visions-into-digital-video-in-historic-experiment--gizmodo/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Sep 2011 01:34:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/scientists-reconstruct-brains-visions-into-digital-video-in-historic-experiment--gizmodo/</guid>
      <description>via gizmodo.com  This is the stuff of Sci-Fi movies. Amazing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Samuel L Ipsum | Alternative Lorem Ipsum Generator</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/samuel-l-ipsum--alternative-lorem-ipsum-generator/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Sep 2011 00:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/samuel-l-ipsum--alternative-lorem-ipsum-generator/</guid>
      <description>  via slipsum.com  Awesome.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ba? Fa! | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ba-fa--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Sep 2011 16:23:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ba-fa--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Amazing illusion.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Osaka Station City fountain</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/osaka-station-city-fountain/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2011 23:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/osaka-station-city-fountain/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  This is making the rounds, so I might as well contribute. Beautiful (and maybe not so hard to do - it&#39;s much like a dot-matrix printer, but printing from bottom up). I saw one of these a few years ago at the Motor Show in Geneva (at the Jeep stand), but it was much lower resolution and much less creative.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go for Launch! | AirSpaceMag.com</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/go-for-launch--airspacemag.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2011 12:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/go-for-launch--airspacemag.com/</guid>
      <description>via airspacemag.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing cfengine on Mac OS X</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-cfengine-on-mac-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 05 Aug 2011 02:31:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-cfengine-on-mac-os-x/</guid>
      <description>Cfengine (tested 3.2.0) installs easily on OS X (tested 10.7), given that it&#39;s Unix. One problem I encountered was that it does not compile with the bundled version of Berkeley DB (it recognizes it during configure, but produces compilation errors). The solution is to use some other DB engine. I chose Tokyo Cabinet. Using homebrew, the process is simple
brew install tokyo-cabinet
After this, configure --with-tokyocabinet, and then compile and install as usual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emacs - Multiple columns one buffer - Stack Overflow</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/emacs---multiple-columns-one-buffer---stack-overflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2011 18:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/emacs---multiple-columns-one-buffer---stack-overflow/</guid>
      <description>Follow mode is a minor mode that makes two windows, both showing the same buffer, scroll as a single tall “virtual window.” To use Follow mode, go to a frame with just one window, split it into two side-by-side windows using C-x 3, and then type M-x follow-mode. From then on, you can edit the buffer in either of the two windows, or scroll either one; the other window follows it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>‪Space Shuttle: The complete missions -- by Nature Video‬‏ - YouTube</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/space-shuttle-the-complete-missions----by-nature-video---youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 16:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/space-shuttle-the-complete-missions----by-nature-video---youtube/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Beautiful video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My thoughts about the Lion upgrade process</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-thoughts-about-the-lion-upgrade-process/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2011 10:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-thoughts-about-the-lion-upgrade-process/</guid>
      <description>I just finished upgrading our Mac (my wife and I share it) to Lion. It looks very nice. This has been the OS X upgrade to which I have given less thought: purchase, download, backup, install, done.
 I think a lot of this has to do with the online distribution. We are used to installing things downloaded from the Internet without much thought (of course there are security considerations, but that&#39;s another topic).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Karate Exam</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/karate-exam/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2011 19:03:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/karate-exam/</guid>
      <description>
  Today I had my 2nd-Kyu Karate exam. I passed! This is my first exam after having abandoned karate for 10 years and coming back to training 5 months ago, so I&#39;m very happy that it went well. Here&#39;s the &#34;after&#34; photo. I am the one with the headband (and yes, I am the oldest in the group other than my Sensei). </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My money-making setup in PvZ. Just let it run and it collects coins for the longest time :)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-money-making-setup-in-pvz.-just-let-it-run-and-it-collects-coins-for-the-longest-time-/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jun 2011 22:12:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-money-making-setup-in-pvz.-just-let-it-run-and-it-collects-coins-for-the-longest-time-/</guid>
      <description>
  via Tweetbot for iPhone  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little useful feature in Outlook: &#34;you are not responding to the latest message in this conversation&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/little-useful-feature-in-outlook-you-are-not-responding-to-the-latest-message-in-this-conversation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2011 13:18:33 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/little-useful-feature-in-outlook-you-are-not-responding-to-the-latest-message-in-this-conversation/</guid>
      <description>As annoying as Outlook is most of the time, it has a few nifty features. For example, this notification:
 appears at the top of a compose window when appropriate. It is very useful because it appears if, while you are typing a message, another one comes into the same thread, thus reducing occurrences of &#34;crossed&#34; (and possibly conflicting) responses. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The stark beauty of Cassini’s Saturn | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-stark-beauty-of-cassinis-saturn--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2011 13:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-stark-beauty-of-cassinis-saturn--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Amazing short video. Make sure you enable HD, hit play, then pause, and let it download entirely before resuming, so you can watch it without interruptions. And make it full screen!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Swingin’ physics | Bad Astronomy | Discover Magazine</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/swingin-physics--bad-astronomy--discover-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2011 16:30:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/swingin-physics--bad-astronomy--discover-magazine/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Very nice video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiny Wings review</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/tiny-wings-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 May 2011 09:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/tiny-wings-review/</guid>
      <description>I hate this game. I hate it so much. I don’t want to play it. I hate playing it. I don’t enjoy playing it. But every day [...] I play it. I cry and I throw a tantrum and I complain and I hate it so much, but I play it.
Go to hell, Andreas Illiger. You rich, genius son of a bitch.
 via log.maniacalrage.net  My feelings exactly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Back from vacation</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/back-from-vacation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Apr 2011 09:32:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/back-from-vacation/</guid>
      <description>
  We had a few days of true rest and relaxation at the beach. Very very nice. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Getting closer to the beach</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/getting-closer-to-the-beach/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2011 11:10:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/getting-closer-to-the-beach/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cleaning the cobra pit</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cleaning-the-cobra-pit/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2011 01:46:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cleaning-the-cobra-pit/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Scary and amazing. He seems so calm!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Physics engines for dummies | Paul&#39;s blog@Wildbunny</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/physics-engines-for-dummies--pauls-blogwildbunny/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Apr 2011 11:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/physics-engines-for-dummies--pauls-blogwildbunny/</guid>
      <description>This time i’m going to talk about the basic components that make up a physics engine and how to put them together; this tutorial is aimed at programmers who have a basic grasp of maths and geometry but would like to step into the world of simulation.
It is my hope that if, at the beginning of this article, you are able to code the physics behind the 1972 game Pong, by the end of the article you will be equally happy writing your own constraints to use in your own physics solver!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The new Commodore 64</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-new-commodore-64/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2011 23:57:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-new-commodore-64/</guid>
      <description>  via commodoreusa.net  I SO want one.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The baboon&#39;s guide to the internet: Michael Jordan</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-baboons-guide-to-the-internet-michael-jordan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2011 10:20:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-baboons-guide-to-the-internet-michael-jordan/</guid>
      <description> via baboonsguide.blogspot.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dog Sledding season - coming to a close - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/dog-sledding-season---coming-to-a-close---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2011 12:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/dog-sledding-season---coming-to-a-close---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  Another beautiful set of pictures from TBP.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Concrete Poured Into Ant Colony Reveals Insect Megalopolis</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/concrete-poured-into-ant-colony-reveals-insect-megalopolis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 15:46:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/concrete-poured-into-ant-colony-reveals-insect-megalopolis/</guid>
      <description> via theatlantic.com  Amazing. Looks like something from an Alien movie.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically creating tasks from email in Outlook</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/automatically-creating-tasks-from-email-in-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 01:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/automatically-creating-tasks-from-email-in-outlook/</guid>
      <description>Please note: I am no longer using Windows nor Outlook, so unfortunately I cannot offer any help with problems you encounter using these scripts and techniques.
Over the last few days I have been redoing my GTD-under-Outlook setup, based on the instructions available in the &#34;GTD and Outlook&#34; guide from DavidCo (I will write more about my setup later). One of the tricks the guide suggest is creating a mail rule on outgoing mail, which scans the message body for a special tag (/wf or *wf* are suggested) and automatically adds the message to the @WAITING FOR email folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Open Penetration Testing Bookmarks Collection</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/open-penetration-testing-bookmarks-collection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2011 00:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/open-penetration-testing-bookmarks-collection/</guid>
      <description>Open Penetration Testing Bookmarks Collection via code.google.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Flight of the AirJelly /via @biz</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-flight-of-the-airjelly-/via-biz/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2011 22:07:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-flight-of-the-airjelly-/via-biz/</guid>
      <description> via talkingscience.org  What a cool robot.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Overhauling my GTD system under Windows</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/overhauling-my-gtd-system-under-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2011 00:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/overhauling-my-gtd-system-under-windows/</guid>
      <description>As you may know, I&#39;m a reluctant switcher from Mac to Windows. I am also a fan of GTD. I had been using Jello Dashboard (JD) to implement GTD under Outlook. JD is a very nice system, the developer is friendly and responsive, and I had even written several patches to adapt it to my way of working. I was even in the process of drafting a series of blog posts titled &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to digitally sign a macro project - Outlook</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-digitally-sign-a-macro-project---outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2011 00:16:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-digitally-sign-a-macro-project---outlook/</guid>
      <description>This article explains how you can digitally sign a file or a macro project by using a certificate. If you don&#39;t already have a digital certificate, you must obtain one. To test macro projects on your own computer, you can create your own self-signing certificate by using the Selfcert.exe tool.
 via office.microsoft.com  Useful for future reference. I&#39;m playing with a bit of VBA in Outlook, and found that my code would work fine right after writing it, but if I restart Outlook, the macros will be disabled unless I first sign them as described in this article.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Single-tap conference dialing in iOS 4.3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/single-tap-conference-dialing-in-ios-4.3/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 17:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/single-tap-conference-dialing-in-ios-4.3/</guid>
      <description>Apple released iOS 4.3 a few days ago, and if you follow this topic at all, you have probably already heard all about the Personal Hotspot feature, AirPlay enhancements, and whatnot. But buried in the notes for this release was a new feature that caught my attention:
Single tap conference call dialing with a pause to send a passcode
 I have found almost no mentions of this new feature online (most reviews focus on the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrifying Japan Tsunami video (via Bad Astronomy)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/terrifying-japan-tsunami-video-via-bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Mar 2011 01:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/terrifying-japan-tsunami-video-via-bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>
Yes, those are buildings on fire as they are being swept along with the water. That is one of the most terrifying, horrifying things I have ever seen.
 via blogs.discovermagazine.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nyiragongo Crater: Journey to the Center of the World - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/nyiragongo-crater-journey-to-the-center-of-the-world---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 10:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/nyiragongo-crater-journey-to-the-center-of-the-world---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  Amazing pictures of an incredibly dangerous expedition. Just look at the guy in the photo above, standing at the very edge of a lava lake. Click through for more beautiful pictures.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ET Sequel: &#34;ET-X&#34; (Extended Trailer)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/et-sequel-et-x-extended-trailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 10:45:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/et-sequel-et-x-extended-trailer/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Very nicely done :)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ridiculously awesome pic of Discovery and the ISS taken from the ground! | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ridiculously-awesome-pic-of-discovery-and-the-iss-taken-from-the-ground--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Feb 2011 10:37:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ridiculously-awesome-pic-of-discovery-and-the-iss-taken-from-the-ground--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>  via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Simply incredible that someone can get a picture like this from the ground.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazing Shuttle launch video from an airplane window</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/amazing-shuttle-launch-video-from-an-airplane-window/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Feb 2011 22:43:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/amazing-shuttle-launch-video-from-an-airplane-window/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Just amazing.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ken Jennings describes what it&#39;s like to play against a machine - Slate Magazine</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ken-jennings-describes-what-its-like-to-play-against-a-machine---slate-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 21:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ken-jennings-describes-what-its-like-to-play-against-a-machine---slate-magazine/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Watching you on Jeopardy! is what inspired the whole project,&#34; one IBM engineer told me, consolingly. &#34;And we looked at your games over and over, your style of play. There&#39;s a lot of you in Watson.&#34; I understood then why the engineers wanted to beat me so badly: To them, I wasn&#39;t the good guy, playing for the human race. That was Watson&#39;s role, as a symbol and product of human innovation and ingenuity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Calling on RoboCop to Help Detroit - NYTimes.com</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/calling-on-robocop-to-help-detroit---nytimes.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 21:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/calling-on-robocop-to-help-detroit---nytimes.com/</guid>
      <description>     Yet in a city where some of the most prominent buildings have sat vacant for decades and booting a scandal-plagued mayor out of office took eight months, raising $50,000 to produce and install a 7-foot-tall iron replica of the crime-fighting cyborg was accomplished in a mere six days.
  via nytimes.com  Of course, the people of Detroit have their priorities right :)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>IBM Watson: Final Jeopardy! and the Future of Watson</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ibm-watson-final-jeopardy-and-the-future-of-watson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Feb 2011 11:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ibm-watson-final-jeopardy-and-the-future-of-watson/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Amazing feat, incredible technology. Congratulations to the Watson team!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Thing Isn’t Going To Park Itse….Oh - There, I Fixed It - Redneck Repairs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/this-thing-isnt-going-to-park-itse.oh---there-i-fixed-it---redneck-repairs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Feb 2011 10:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/this-thing-isnt-going-to-park-itse.oh---there-i-fixed-it---redneck-repairs/</guid>
      <description> via thereifixedit.failblog.org  Very impressive.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untitled 4</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Feb 2011 16:54:46 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-4/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Game&#39;s on!</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/games-on/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2011 14:42:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/games-on/</guid>
      <description>  
Taken at John F. Kennedy </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Impact | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/impact--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 17:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/impact--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description> 
It’s an impressive animation of what would happen if an asteroid — maybe 100 500 miles across or so — impacts the Earth. The visuals are stunning, and someone set it to excellent music for the action
 via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Scary stuff, very well done.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pakistan: daily life - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pakistan-daily-life---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2011 14:05:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pakistan-daily-life---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  Beautiful, sometimes heart-breaking photos. Kids are kids anywhere, play and laugh and cry, but no kid should have to live in the poverty shown in some of these pictures.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The real Star Wars - ReflectionOf.Me</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-real-star-wars---reflectionof.me/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Feb 2011 22:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-real-star-wars---reflectionof.me/</guid>
      <description> via reflectionof.me  Great photo.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sagan destroys astrology</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/sagan-destroys-astrology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Feb 2011 15:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/sagan-destroys-astrology/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  &#34;Crumbly&#34;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zheng Lab - Bad Project (Lady Gaga parody)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/zheng-lab---bad-project-lady-gaga-parody/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2011 01:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/zheng-lab---bad-project-lady-gaga-parody/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Awesome video. Every grad student I know has felt like this at some point.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>100 Years of IBM - ReflectionOf.Me</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/100-years-of-ibm---reflectionof.me/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2011 10:09:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/100-years-of-ibm---reflectionof.me/</guid>
      <description> via reflectionof.me  Very nice video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to fix &#34;texexpand error: More than one input file specified&#34; in latex2html</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-fix-texexpand-error-more-than-one-input-file-specified-in-latex2html/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2011 00:24:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-fix-texexpand-error-more-than-one-input-file-specified-in-latex2html/</guid>
      <description>There&#39;s a bug that causes problems when running latex2html on files which have spaces in the path. The workaround is to either move things to folders with no spaces, or add appropriate symbolic links.via ubuntuforums.org  This error had me stumped in trying to process a latex file with latex2html:texexpand: Error: More than one input file specified.texexpand failed: No such file or directoryThe fix is simple - make sure the path of the current directory does not have any spaces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing latex2html under Win7 with cygwin</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-latex2html-under-win7-with-cygwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 15:28:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-latex2html-under-win7-with-cygwin/</guid>
      <description>I got latex2html to install on the latest cygwin, however to get the configure to pass I had to alter the configure to recognize cygwin as a UNIX. via mail-archive.com  Using this patch I was able to properly configure and install latex2html under cygwin in Windows 7.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LogParser, Event Logs, and Vista - Neil Carpenter&#39;s Blog - Site Home - TechNet Blogs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/logparser-event-logs-and-vista---neil-carpenters-blog---site-home---technet-blogs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2011 12:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/logparser-event-logs-and-vista---neil-carpenters-blog---site-home---technet-blogs/</guid>
      <description>The only workaround to this is to convert the logfile to the new evtx format prior to parsing it. You can do this in the event log viewer GUI by doing a Save As... but I find it easier to do this at the command prompt: wevtutil epl application.evt application.evtx /lf:true
  via blogs.technet.com  I&#39;m trying to process Windows Event Viewer files (.evt) from some servers on my Win7 machine, which kept me giving a &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Canadian TV slams homeopathy | Bad Astronomy | Discover Magazine</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/canadian-tv-slams-homeopathy--bad-astronomy--discover-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jan 2011 09:55:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/canadian-tv-slams-homeopathy--bad-astronomy--discover-magazine/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  If you still somehow believe homeopathy works, please do yourself a favor and watch this program.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Annals of commerce « The Reality-Based Community</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/annals-of-commerce--the-reality-based-community/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2010 11:44:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/annals-of-commerce--the-reality-based-community/</guid>
      <description>Nestlé pods, pal; it’s a lifetime relationship. That $500 machine is a down payment on a 400-900% tax on every cup of coffee you make with it: three cups a day and you pay for the machine again, or more, every year you own it. Next, a frying pan customized to work only with a single brand of eggs, yup.via samefacts.com  I don&#39;t understand the popularity of those pod-fed coffee machines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dinner for One</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/dinner-for-one/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Dec 2010 00:31:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/dinner-for-one/</guid>
      <description> via executiveroadwarrior.com  Somehow in all my time living in Switzerland I never heard of or watched this clip, but it is very funny.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>December 2010 Blizzard Timelapse on Vimeo</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/december-2010-blizzard-timelapse-on-vimeo/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 23:54:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/december-2010-blizzard-timelapse-on-vimeo/</guid>
      <description> via vimeo.com  Impressive.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detexify LaTeX handwritten symbol recognition</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/detexify-latex-handwritten-symbol-recognition/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2010 12:34:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/detexify-latex-handwritten-symbol-recognition/</guid>
      <description>How do I use it?  Just draw the symbol you are looking for into the square area above and look what happens!
 via detexify.kirelabs.org  Fantastic tool. Draw a symbol, and it gives you suggestions for LaTeX symbols that match what you drew.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up a global hotkey to add tasks to Outlook</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/setting-up-a-global-hotkey-to-add-tasks-to-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2010 12:14:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/setting-up-a-global-hotkey-to-add-tasks-to-outlook/</guid>
      <description>One thing I missed since I moved from a Mac (using The Hit List for GTD) to Outlook (using Jello Dashboard for GTD) was the availability of a global hot key that I could use to bring up a text entry box which I could use to quickly add things into my electronic Inbox, for later processing.
I have found a way to achieve this, and here is the setup I am using now:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTD tip: clean up physical clutter using ziploc bags</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/gtd-tip-clean-up-physical-clutter-using-ziploc-bags/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Dec 2010 17:46:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/gtd-tip-clean-up-physical-clutter-using-ziploc-bags/</guid>
      <description>If you are like me, you carry in your backpack, bag or briefcase all sorts of physical stuff, other than documents, papers or magazines. You know the type: phone chargers, USB cables, power adapters, network cables, USB sticks and other small gadgets or accessories. Over time these things accumulate and it becomes harder and harder to find them and to keep them organized. 
I have been using a low-tech tool for organizing these things: ziploc bags.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Translation on the fly</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/translation-on-the-fly/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 21:57:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/translation-on-the-fly/</guid>
      <description>When I arrived in Switzerland nine years ago I didn&#39;t speak a word of German (much less Swiss German!), so for a while I faced a very real and practical problem. I would encounter signs on the street, and have absolutely no idea what they meant. Does this sign mean I can pass, or I cannot? &#34;Watch your step&#34; or &#34;Watch for the vicious dog&#34;? During that period, I often wished for a gadget that I could point at the sign and would give me an instant translation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untitled 3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 17:35:30 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-3/</guid>
      <description>   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Filmography 2010 compilation</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/filmography-2010-compilation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2010 12:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/filmography-2010-compilation/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Incredible compilation, very nicely done. So many movies, so little time. I haven&#39;t seen even a tenth of the movies shown here (mostly I&#39;ve seen the animated ones, since go to the movies more often with the girls than without).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nice day, also my first instagr.am shot</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/nice-day-also-my-first-instagr.am-shot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 13 Dec 2010 21:04:05 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/nice-day-also-my-first-instagr.am-shot/</guid>
      <description>  
Taken at Parque Bicentenario </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Day at the park with the girls</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/day-at-the-park-with-the-girls/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2010 12:16:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/day-at-the-park-with-the-girls/</guid>
      <description>
         </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My home office, right now</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-home-office-right-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2010 09:53:50 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-home-office-right-now/</guid>
      <description>
  No filtering or cleanup whatsoever. Yes, it&#39;s a bit of a mess, I haven&#39;t fully cleaned up since we moved. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing PicPosterous</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/testing-picposterous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2010 08:03:49 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/testing-picposterous/</guid>
      <description>
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Let it snow! - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/let-it-snow---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2010 11:08:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/let-it-snow---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  I am sooooo happy to be back in Mexico where I don&#39;t have to deal with snow :)OTOH, there are some beautiful pictures here. Snow can be beautiful, but I think you have to grow with it to really enjoy it. Not my case.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing sshd configuration files with cfengine3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/editing-sshd-configuration-files-with-cfengine3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 23:30:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/editing-sshd-configuration-files-with-cfengine3/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s a cfengine bundle that I wrote for editing the sshd configuration file by passing an array with the parameters. Using an array is a very elegant way of defining the values to set. The bundle also restarts sshd after any changes are made, unless the no_restarts class is defined.
The first gist contains the edit_sshd bundle itself, together with the set_config_values bundle that actually performs the editing job (this should go into a library file, I have it in my personal version of cfengine_stdlib.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Symphony of Science</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/symphony-of-science/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2010 00:59:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/symphony-of-science/</guid>
      <description>via symphonyofscience.com  If you haven&#39;t, go see these videos.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>docco.coffee, Rocco, etc.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/docco.coffee-rocco-etc./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 23:56:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/docco.coffee-rocco-etc./</guid>
      <description>Docco is a quick-and-dirty, hundred-line-long, literate-programming-style documentation generator. It produces HTML that displays your comments alongside your code. Comments are passed through Markdown, and code is passed through Pygments syntax highlighting. via jashkenas.github.com  Nice-looking tool for literate programming, with variants for several languages.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Want: “GTD Managing Projects” set</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/want-gtd-managing-projects-set/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Nov 2010 21:06:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/want-gtd-managing-projects-set/</guid>
      <description>  via feedproxy.google.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pidgin cannot connect to MSN: the certificate chain presented is invalid</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pidgin-cannot-connect-to-msn-the-certificate-chain-presented-is-invalid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2010 10:47:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pidgin-cannot-connect-to-msn-the-certificate-chain-presented-is-invalid/</guid>
      <description>1. Deleted all msn/live/hotmail certificates in the folder
2. went to https://omega.contacts.msn.com using fire fox (https not http)
3. right click &amp;gt; view page INFO &amp;gt; Security Tab &amp;gt; View Certificate Button &amp;gt; Details Tab &amp;gt; Export Button
4. Saved the file to ~.purple/certificates/x509/tls_peers/omega.contacts.msn.com
5. Reconnected
6. Perfect via diarizing.com  Like many people, I started getting certificate errors when connecting to my MSN account using Pidgin. The straightforward fix described (delete certificate, reconnect to fetch the new one) didn&#39;t work for me with Pidgin 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Running Shells in Emacs: An Overview | Mastering Emacs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/running-shells-in-emacs-an-overview--mastering-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Nov 2010 00:52:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/running-shells-in-emacs-an-overview--mastering-emacs/</guid>
      <description>If you use Emacs as your shell you will have all the functionality that Emacs provides plus you get almost all of the advantages provided by the shell itself, but built into Emacs. This article is only a quick overview of all the shells: I plan on tackling each one, in-depth, later on. via masteringemacs.org  Nice overview, I hadn&#39;t heard of several of the more advanced shell modes.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2010 World Fencing Championships - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2010-world-fencing-championships---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Nov 2010 02:26:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2010-world-fencing-championships---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via The Big Picture  Great fencing photos. Make me miss my fencing days.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Knight Arts | Random Acts of Culture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/knight-arts--random-acts-of-culture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2010 23:38:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/knight-arts--random-acts-of-culture/</guid>
      <description>
via knightarts.org  What do you get when you combine Improv Everywhere with opera? Random Acts of Culture.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The boiling, erupting Sun | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-boiling-erupting-sun--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Oct 2010 09:41:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-boiling-erupting-sun--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description>
They look so delicate, probably because they make the Sun look fuzzy, like a comfy blanket… but have no doubts on the fury and scale of what you’re seeing here. See that little bright spot on the plume on the left, just above the Sun’s edge? That spot is the same size as the Earth
 via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Amazing photograph of the sun.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The most amazing WWF play I have ever seen</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-most-amazing-wwf-play-i-have-ever-seen/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Oct 2010 00:47:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-most-amazing-wwf-play-i-have-ever-seen/</guid>
      <description>
 185 points! Just incredible. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How high is space?</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-high-is-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 02:18:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-high-is-space/</guid>
      <description> via feedproxy.google.com  Amazing infographic. Make sure you follow the link through to the full version (the image shown here is just a small part of it).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science, Reason and Critical Thinking: A Handy Alternative Therapy Flowchart</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/science-reason-and-critical-thinking-a-handy-alternative-therapy-flowchart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Oct 2010 00:52:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/science-reason-and-critical-thinking-a-handy-alternative-therapy-flowchart/</guid>
      <description>  via crispian-jago.blogspot.com  Hilarious. Make sure you look at the big version.&#34;Acceptable risk?&#34; -&amp;gt; &#34;Setting head on fire&#34; -&amp;gt; &#34;Ear candling&#34;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Edward Horsford Creates Amazing Bursting Balloons Photographs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/edward-horsford-creates-amazing-bursting-balloons-photographs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Oct 2010 01:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/edward-horsford-creates-amazing-bursting-balloons-photographs/</guid>
      <description> via diyphotography.net  Very nice photos of exploding water balloons (see the link for an interview with the author).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;It&#39;s just eating somebody&#39;s tree --- 10-4&#34;</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/its-just-eating-somebodys-tree-----10-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Oct 2010 13:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/its-just-eating-somebodys-tree-----10-4/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Hilarious.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Homemade Spacecraft</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/homemade-spacecraft/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2010 13:22:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/homemade-spacecraft/</guid>
      <description> via vimeo.com  A father and his son send a camera into space using a weather balloon. Absolutely amazing experiment and video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pac-Man Spotted In The Wild</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pac-man-spotted-in-the-wild/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Oct 2010 21:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pac-man-spotted-in-the-wild/</guid>
      <description>Jaime &#34;Kalapusa&#34; Margary, who&#39;s given us realistic Piranha Plants, and Super Mario fungi in the past, now turns his attention to Pac-Man, presently soaking in jar of formaldehyde.
Writes Jaime:
The idea behind the video is Pac Man&#39;s final days, free from the maze (kudos if you can guess who&#39;s castle that is) and eating pellets to his heart&#39;s content in a glowing pellet forest. His dead, bloated body is found afterwards and then delivered to 8-Bit Labs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Making cygwin, Windows and emacs understand the same symlinks</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/making-cygwin-windows-and-emacs-understand-the-same-symlinks/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 09:39:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/making-cygwin-windows-and-emacs-understand-the-same-symlinks/</guid>
      <description>Today I ran into the problem that symlinks created under cygwin using &#34;ln -s&#34; are not understood by Windows, and of course Windows shortcuts are seen by cygwin as regular files. Happily, this is a (semi-)solved problem. For reference, this is what needs to be done:

 Add &#34;winsymlinks&#34; to your CYGWIN environment variable. For example, in my .bashrc I have the following:
export CYGWIN=&#34;nodosfilewarning winsymlinks&#34;

This makes cygwin create symlinks differently, in a form that is understood both by it and by Windows.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Website redesign and unification</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/website-redesign-and-unification/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 02:22:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/website-redesign-and-unification/</guid>
      <description>There are still some rough edges, but by far the redesign and unification of zzamboni.org is done. With the same design you can now find my blogs (hosted by posterous.com), my project pages (hosted in github.com project repositories) and some static pages (hosted in my personal github.com pages repository, this includes the root, About and Code pages, as well as the static copy of my old blog BrT, which is the only one that retains its original design).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fall is in the air - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fall-is-in-the-air---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Sep 2010 00:09:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fall-is-in-the-air---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  I love the fall, even more now that I know it won&#39;t be followed by a crude winter :) Still, I miss some of the Swiss scenery and traditions. Beautiful photos from TBP, as usual.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This is a news website article about a scientific finding</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/this-is-a-news-website-article-about-a-scientific-finding/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 22:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/this-is-a-news-website-article-about-a-scientific-finding/</guid>
      <description>In the standfirst I will make a fairly obvious pun about the subject matter before posing an inane question I have no intention of really answering: is this an important scientific finding?
 via guardian.co.uk  Brilliant. Reminds me of The Ultimately Publishable Computer Science Paper of the 90s.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DGSCA se convierte en TIC</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/dgsca-se-convierte-en-tic/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2010 10:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/dgsca-se-convierte-en-tic/</guid>
      <description>Por acuerdo del Dr. José Narro Robles, Rector de la Universidad Nacional Autónoma de México, a partir del 27 de septiembre de 2010 la Dirección General de Servicios de Cómputo Académico cambia de denominación a Dirección General de Cómputo y de Tecnologías de Información y Comunicación, y el sitio Web de esta dependencia es:
  via dgsca.unam.mx  El final de una era. Yo comencé mi carrera profesional en DGSCA, por lo que tengo muchos recuerdos asociados con ese nombre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>La UNAM cumple 100 años</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/la-unam-cumple-100-a%C3%B1os/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2010 12:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/la-unam-cumple-100-a%C3%B1os/</guid>
      <description>Si hubiera que reducir a la UNAM a unas cuantas cifras esenciales, tendrían que anotarse, entre otras, las siguientes: 314 mil alumnos, 35 mil académicos, tres mil 500 investigadores, 2 mil edificios, 139 bibliotecas, 56 mil computadoras conectadas en red, 18 museos, otros tantos recintos históricos, un canal de televisión y una estación de radio, una casa editora de miles de libros y de cientos de publicaciones periódicas, así como una Ciudad Universitaria que ha sido declarada por la UNESCO Patrimonio de la Humanidad.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cool - Google&#39;s logo today is about Mexico&#39;s Independence Bicentenary</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cool---googles-logo-today-is-about-mexicos-independence-bicentenary/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2010 09:55:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cool---googles-logo-today-is-about-mexicos-independence-bicentenary/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Texas Sharpshooter Fallacy « You Are Not So Smart</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-texas-sharpshooter-fallacy--you-are-not-so-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Sep 2010 02:44:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-texas-sharpshooter-fallacy--you-are-not-so-smart/</guid>
      <description>If you have a human brain, you do this all of the time. Picking out clusters of coincidence is a predictable malfunction of normal human logic. via youarenotsosmart.com  We see patterns everywhere, our brain is hardwired to do it. Most of them are harmless or even beneficial. The problem is when people start assigning meaning to the patterns, as explanation of whatever they want to believe or to convince other people of (such as &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woot: Refurbished Coffeenaker - Ewww</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/woot-refurbished-coffeenaker---ewww/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2010 13:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/woot-refurbished-coffeenaker---ewww/</guid>
      <description>Can you taste other people’s saliva, stomach acid, and tooth enamel in it? Certainly not. Will you think about it now that we’ve brought it up? Maybe. But the fact is people buy ‘em so there must be a demand. via sellout.woot.com  Do I want to buy one, after reading this? Probably not.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cfengine3 lexer for Pygments</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine3-lexer-for-pygments/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Sep 2010 21:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine3-lexer-for-pygments/</guid>
      <description>I have written a Cfengine3 lexer for Pygments, the open source syntax-highlighter used by Gist and many other sites. It seems to work fine on all the cfengine policy files I have tested, but if you find anything that doesn&#39;t quite work as expected, please let me know. This is my first-ever Pygments lexer, so if you are an expert and can advise me on better ways of doing things, I&#39;d very much appreciate the feedback too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Scribe-generated prose (aka &#34;Google Scribe channels Kanye West&#34;)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/google-scribe-generated-prose-aka-google-scribe-channels-kanye-west/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 17:21:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/google-scribe-generated-prose-aka-google-scribe-channels-kanye-west/</guid>
      <description>Google has launched a new labs project called Google Scribe, which essentially provides an auto-completion service. You type, it autocompletes. The following text was generated by typing a single space, and from then on simply accepting the default suggestions (pressing &#34;Enter&#34; every time the suggestion popup appeared). I had to stop at some point, but it seems like a good source of mindless entertainment. Also, the result varies depending on the initial seed word you provide, and also on whether you just accept blindly (Enter) or type spaces at certain places.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pacific Sun Cruise liner in very heavy seas. Internal CCTV footage.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pacific-sun-cruise-liner-in-very-heavy-seas.-internal-cctv-footage./</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 16:12:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pacific-sun-cruise-liner-in-very-heavy-seas.-internal-cctv-footage./</guid>
      <description> via liveleak.com  Scary video (entertaining in a schadenfreude way). I found it unsettling that the &#34;horizon&#34; in the video doesn&#39;t move (as it would in a movie scene, for example, to have you notice how much the boat is moving) since the camera is moving with the ship, but you can infer the violence of the swaying from the damage it caused. /via @benthemorrison on Twitter.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The 7 habits of highly effective writers</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-writers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 14:24:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-7-habits-of-highly-effective-writers/</guid>
      <description>Effective writers ...
  Separate the writing and the editing processes.   Focus on the interesting.   Tap into the power of metaphor.   Do adequate research.   Learn from the writing of others.   Write in small bursts.   Read their work out loud.    via ragan.com  Worth reading the full article. I particularly suffer from not following #1 - I always end up losing time over editing details, instead of focusing on the raw content of what I&#39;m writing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Storing CFEngine configuration in CVS</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/storing-cfengine-configuration-in-cvs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2010 14:17:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/storing-cfengine-configuration-in-cvs/</guid>
      <description> via sial.org  Useful article about storing both development and production configurations of cfengine using a version control mechanism. I am in the process of developing a similar setup using git, I will share it here when I get it to work properly.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GTD Tip: one-key opening of INBOX notebook in OneNote</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/gtd-tip-one-key-opening-of-inbox-notebook-in-onenote/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Sep 2010 17:15:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/gtd-tip-one-key-opening-of-inbox-notebook-in-onenote/</guid>
      <description>One of the most useful applications I have discovered since I had to switch to Windows as my main OS is OneNote, a really great note-taking application which I use for pretty much every data-storing and note-taking need. I use a OneNote notebook as part of my GTD inbox. Today&#39;s very simple tip is how to assign a keystroke for opening my Inbox notebook from anywhere in the system. Here are the steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>@BadAstronomer The irony is killing me :-)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/badastronomer-the-irony-is-killing-me--/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 15:44:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/badastronomer-the-irony-is-killing-me--/</guid>
      <description>This was the ad Google placed on the RSS feed entry for one of your recent posts:
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pocketful of Dough - Tips on Tipping</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pocketful-of-dough---tips-on-tipping/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 03:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pocketful-of-dough---tips-on-tipping/</guid>
      <description>“What kind of establishment do you think this is?” “How dare you insult me!” “You think you can get in with that?”
It’s just after 8 p.m. on a balmy summer Saturday and I’m heading toward one of New York’s most overbooked restaurants, Balthazar, where celebrities regularly go to be celebrated and where lay diners like me call a month in advance to try and secure a reservation. I don’t have a reservation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On remembering and dealing with people&#39;s names</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/on-remembering-and-dealing-with-peoples-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Sep 2010 02:20:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/on-remembering-and-dealing-with-peoples-names/</guid>
      <description>A person&#39;s own name is the single most important word to him/her; it is intimately tied to his/her identity as an individual. How you deal with people&#39;s names can have a profound effect on their impressions of you: Think about the times you&#39;ve felt special when someone you admired addressed you by your name in a sincere tone; or think about the times when you&#39;ve felt belittled when someone negligently called you by the wrong name, or worse, maliciously made fun of your name in front of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science, Reason and Critical Thinking: Modern Science Map</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/science-reason-and-critical-thinking-modern-science-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 08:51:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/science-reason-and-critical-thinking-modern-science-map/</guid>
      <description>  via crispian-jago.blogspot.com  This is seriously amazing, a subway-map-style timeline of science. Go look at the full-size image.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GeekTyrant - News - Fan Made SUPERMAN: DOOMSDAY Trailer</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/geektyrant---news---fan-made-superman-doomsdaytrailer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Aug 2010 09:00:16 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/geektyrant---news---fan-made-superman-doomsdaytrailer/</guid>
      <description>
In this fan-edit you&#39;ll get to see the movie that I hope the studios bring to the big screen in a future Superman film. Please no more Lex Luthor centered shenanigans or kryptonite BS... let&#39;s see Superman face a real threat...Doomsday!
 via geektyrant.com  This would be so awesome. I&#39;ve always wanted to see Doomsday in a Superman movie.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hierarchical copying with cfengine3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/hierarchical-copying-with-cfengine3/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Aug 2010 00:28:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/hierarchical-copying-with-cfengine3/</guid>
      <description>I recently posted a snippet to perform hierarchical copying in cfengine3. As I was attempting to integrate this mechanism into my copy of cfengine&#39;s COPBL, I realized that no additional functions or body components are needed. Thanks to cfengine3&#39;s list expansion, all you need to do is include in the existing copy promise the list containing the desired list of suffixes to try. For example:
{% gist 552848 %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying out The Pomodoro Technique</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/trying-out-the-pomodoro-technique/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 10:09:44 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/trying-out-the-pomodoro-technique/</guid>
      <description>The basic unit of work in the Pomodoro Technique™ can be split in five simple steps:  Choose a task to be accomplished Set the Pomodoro to 25 minutes (the Pomodoro is the timer) Work on the task until the Pomodoro rings, then put a check on your sheet of paper Take a short break (5 minutes is OK) Every 4 Pomodoros take a longer break   via pomodorotechnique.com  I&#39;m giving the Pomodoro Technique a try today for my work.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The State of Open Source System Automation</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-state-of-open-source-system-automation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Aug 2010 01:55:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-state-of-open-source-system-automation/</guid>
      <description>The days of DIY system administration are rapidly coming to a close. Why? Because the open source tools available are just too good not to use. Presenting Bcfg2, Cfengine, Chef and Puppet. via linux-mag.com  Nice overview of the Usenix 2010 Configuration Management Summit, including descriptions and comparisons of the four major open-source CM systems.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editing whitespace-separated config files with cfengine</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/editing-whitespace-separated-config-files-with-cfengine/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 01:48:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/editing-whitespace-separated-config-files-with-cfengine/</guid>
      <description>{% gist 548981 %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>cfengine Community Open Promise Body Library on GitHub</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine-community-open-promise-body-library-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 01:37:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cfengine-community-open-promise-body-library-on-github/</guid>
      <description>I have created a copy of the cfengine COPBL on GitHub , where I will use it as a playground for changes and additions. This is in no way endorsed by cfengine - it is just my personal copy. But if you use GitHub and want to use it, go ahead, I will try to keep it updated with respect to the original subversion repository , although it will include my changes too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A sample cfengine policy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-sample-cfengine-policy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Aug 2010 01:11:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-sample-cfengine-policy/</guid>
      <description>
 cf3-findpath2.cf   Actually, this is just to test what posterous does with a text attachment.
Update: so it seems it just attaches it to the page. My suggestion, which I have already emailed to the Posterous guys, is to have the option to auto-post text attachments to gist.github.com. This would make it even easier to include code in blog posts.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Detecting NICs that match certain IP addresses</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/detecting-nics-that-match-certain-ip-addresses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Aug 2010 02:01:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/detecting-nics-that-match-certain-ip-addresses/</guid>
      <description>Another cfengine snippet in case anyone finds it useful. This can be used to determine which NICs in the host have a certain IP address assigned to it, or match any pattern. 
{% gist 547095 %}</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Implementing &#34;single-copy nirvana&#34; in cfengine3</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/implementing-single-copy-nirvana-in-cfengine3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 01:56:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/implementing-single-copy-nirvana-in-cfengine3/</guid>
      <description>Here is a sample implementation in cfengine3 of the technique described in the cfengine wiki as &#34;Singlecopy Nirvana&#34; for cfengine2. Cfengine3 makes the technique more powerful by allowing modularization, so that you can specify both the suffixes to try, and the files to copy using those suffixes, as variables. Also, cf3&#39;s automatic list expansion allows us to write a single copy statement that will be automatically expanded into all the different values to try.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing cfengine on Windows 7 under cygwin</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-cfengine-on-windows-7-under-cygwin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Aug 2010 00:14:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-cfengine-on-windows-7-under-cygwin/</guid>
      <description>Update (2011/09/05): Updated the instructions for cfengine 3.2.0, cygwin 1.7.9, and tested them on a clean cygwin install.
Installing the cfengine community edition under Windows (the commercial version includes native Windows support) is fairly easy under cygwin, you just need to have the appropriate dependencies installed. Here’s how I did it.
Versions 
 cfengine: 3.2.0  Windows 7 Enterprise SP1/64bit cygwin: 1.7.9-1   Additional cygwin packages needed To install these, run cygwin’s setup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pixar How We Do It</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/pixar-how-we-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2010 23:48:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/pixar-how-we-do-it/</guid>
      <description> via pixar.com  Interesting overview of the process.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Chamber: Equal Pay “a Fetish for Money,” Women Should “Choose the Right Partner at Home”</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/us-chamber-equal-pay-a-fetish-for-money-women-should-choose-the-right-partner-at-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Aug 2010 10:53:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/us-chamber-equal-pay-a-fetish-for-money-women-should-choose-the-right-partner-at-home/</guid>
      <description>The US Chamber of Commerce has apparently spent too much time watching Mad Men: in a blog post this morning, Chamber blogger Brad Peck called women’s fight for pay equity to be nothing more than a “fetish for money,” and said women complaining about their pay should focus instead on “choosing the right partner at home.” via workinprogress.firedoglake.com  You couldn&#39;t make up stuff like this. Wow.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;West Wing&#34; - Biblical Quotes</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/west-wing---biblical-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 23:07:02 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/west-wing---biblical-quotes/</guid>
      <description>How to shut up a religious fanatic. 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Grabcartoons v2.7</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/grabcartoons-v2.7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Aug 2010 15:22:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/grabcartoons-v2.7/</guid>
      <description>Last night I made a new release of my comic aggregator script, grabcartoons. You can fetch it from it brand new web page, now hosted by github.com instead of sourceforge.net. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Emulate vi&#39;s % command (jump to matching parenthesis) in Emacs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/emulate-vis--command-jump-to-matching-parenthesis-in-emacs/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Aug 2010 16:09:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/emulate-vis--command-jump-to-matching-parenthesis-in-emacs/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing AucTeX on EmacsW32 on Win7/64bit</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-auctex-on-emacsw32-on-win7/64bit/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Aug 2010 02:36:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-auctex-on-emacsw32-on-win7/64bit/</guid>
      <description>Today I had to install AucTeX to use on my Win7/64 machine under EmacsW32. I found the basic instructions here: http://www.sturmnet.org/blog/2007/09/01/installing-auctex-in-emacsw32, but I had to modify them a bit (in particular, I am using tetex installed from cygwin instead of MiKTeX). Here are the commands I used:
$ mkdir -p /usr/local/share/texmf
$ ./configure --prefix=&#39;c:/Program Files (x86)/Emacs/emacs&#39; --with-texmf-dir=&#39;/usr/local/share/texmf&#39; --with-lispdir=&#39;c:/Program Files (x86)/Emacs/emacs/site-lisp&#39;
$ make
$ make install
I then added the following lines to my C:\Program Files (x86)\Emacs\site-lisp\site-start.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public APIs availability - uptime and down time - slow performance</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/public-apis-availability---uptime-and-down-time---slow-performance/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 16:12:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/public-apis-availability---uptime-and-down-time---slow-performance/</guid>
      <description>   Uptime status Public APIs   via api-status.com  Useful information.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated server and service setup</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/updated-server-and-service-setup/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Aug 2010 14:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/updated-server-and-service-setup/</guid>
      <description>(a friend asked me about my online setup, and I wrote the text below. Then I realized it would also make an interesting blog post, and I just copied and pasted it, with minimal editing, into an email to posterous. This is why I love posterous, it makes posting so easy) 
For my setup, I have a hodgepodge of stuff all aggregated under the zzamboni.org domain. I wrote a blog post about my setup some time ago: http://blog.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploying multiple environments on Heroku (while still hosting code on Github)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/deploying-multiple-environments-on-heroku-while-still-hosting-code-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2010 16:55:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/deploying-multiple-environments-on-heroku-while-still-hosting-code-on-github/</guid>
      <description>
In this post, I will explain how I use Github to version my code and Heroku to deploy it, with 2 different environments. You may also read this article that explains how to deploy your application on Heroku and this one that also explain how to deal with multiple environments
 via suitmymind.com  Nice article, possibly useful reference in the future.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Catharsis</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/catharsis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 16:39:25 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/catharsis/</guid>
      <description> The Misconception: Venting your anger is an effective way to reduce stress and prevent lashing out at friends and family.
The Truth: Venting increases aggressive behavior over time.
 via youarenotsosmart.com  Another excellent article from YANSS, dispelling one of the most-commonly held beliefs in anger management.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>West Lafayette on Failblog</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/west-lafayette-on-failblog/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2010 01:01:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/west-lafayette-on-failblog/</guid>
      <description>via feedproxy.google.com  I found it funny, since I used to live in West Lafayette.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 big ideas from GTD</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/10-big-ideas-from-gtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 14:04:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/10-big-ideas-from-gtd/</guid>
      <description>Here are 10 big ideas from David Allen’s Getting Things Done…
1. If your day-to-day life is out of control, it’s almost impossible to think strategically or plan effectively. 2. Define what being “done” looks like.
3. Mental work has five distinct phases: Collect, Process, Organize, Do, and Review
4. Get everything out of your head.
5. Projects and tasks are two different things: track them separately.
6. Focus on the Next Action required to move forward.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anchoring Effect « You Are Not So Smart</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/anchoring-effect--you-are-not-so-smart/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2010 13:56:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/anchoring-effect--you-are-not-so-smart/</guid>
      <description>You walk into a clothing store and see what is probably the most bad ass leather jacket you’ve ever seen.
You try it on, look in the mirror and decide you must have it. While wearing this item, you imagine onlookers will clutch their chests and gasp every time you walk into a room or cross a street. You lift the sleeve to check the price – $1,000.
Well, that’s that, you think.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Layer 8: The exception IS the rule</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/layer-8-the-exception-is-the-rule/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2010 10:55:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/layer-8-the-exception-is-the-rule/</guid>
      <description>Whenever you look at a firewall rule, half the time you’re going to be asking yourself, “Why is that there? Did *I* put it there? Do we still need it?” It would sure be nice if the explanation were right there, as a comment that could be version-tracked, exported into nice reports, searched on, and placed in a standard format that would be compatible with other exception entries in other tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drowning Doesn&#39;t Look Like Drowning</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/drowning-doesnt-look-like-drowning/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Jul 2010 13:47:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/drowning-doesnt-look-like-drowning/</guid>
      <description>of the approximately 750 children who will drown next year, about 375 of them will do so within 25 yards of a parent or other adult. In ten percent of those drownings, the adult will actually watch them do it, having no idea it is happening (source: CDC). Drowning does not look like drowning via mariovittone.com  This is an eye-opening article for me. Not having actually watched anyone drown (fortunately), I had the impression that someone drowning would trash madly as shown on TV and movies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rands In Repose: How to Write a Book</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/rands-in-repose-how-to-write-a-book/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2010 12:54:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/rands-in-repose-how-to-write-a-book/</guid>
      <description>So, stop. It’s the only sure-fire way to begin. via randsinrepose.com  Very interesting post from Rands about the process of writing a book.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Patent pending. NEW iPhone 4 antenna booster!...</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/patent-pending.-new-iphone-4-antenna-booster.../</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2010 12:09:43 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/patent-pending.-new-iphone-4-antenna-booster.../</guid>
      <description> via marco.org  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Folders in iOS4</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/folders-in-ios4/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2010 16:31:50 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/folders-in-ios4/</guid>
      <description>Thanks to folders in iOS4, I have been able to reduce my iPod Touch from 8 screens to just 2. Very nice :-)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Site improvements</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/site-improvements/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Jun 2010 02:15:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/site-improvements/</guid>
      <description>In their quest to offer a better service every day, the guys at posterous.com have released their Pages tool, which makes it much easier to use Posterous for all my online content by allowing the creation of static pages. And in a stroke of genius, they even allow pages to automatically redirect to arbitrary URLs! This makes it almost trivial to integrate multiple sites into a single, unified user experience. As a first step, as you can see above, I have better integrated this blog and my zznippets blog by giving them a common theme, differentiated only by color.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Just-World Fallacy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-just-world-fallacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2010 11:41:51 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-just-world-fallacy/</guid>
      <description>It is common in fiction for the bad guys to lose and the good guys to win.
It’s how you would like to see the world- just and fair.
In psychology, the tendency to believe this is how the real world actually works is called the Just-World Fallacy.
More specifically, this is the tendency to react to horrible misfortune, like homelessness or drug addiction, by believing the people stuck in horrible situations must have done something to deserve it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Services Menu for iPhone</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-services-menu-for-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Jun 2010 15:34:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-services-menu-for-iphone/</guid>
      <description>On the Mac, Services are a niche. On iPhone OS they’d be nothing short of a revolution. via releasecandidateone.com  Very interesting idea, would be incredibly useful. Follow the link for a full description, plus a mock-up video of how it could work.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>D8 Video: Apple CEO Steve Jobs on Adobe Flash</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/d8-video-apple-ceo-steve-jobs-on-adobe-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 13:11:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/d8-video-apple-ceo-steve-jobs-on-adobe-flash/</guid>
      <description> via d8.allthingsd.com  Nice video summary of Jobs&#39; appearance at D8. Favorite quote: &#34;we&#39;ve sold an iPad every three seconds since launch, so people seem to be liking them&#34;.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The IBM Muppet Show</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-ibm-muppet-show/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Jun 2010 02:40:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-ibm-muppet-show/</guid>
      <description>via technologizer.com  Awesome. IBM used to hire Jim Henson for commercials and training videos.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Deleting my Facebook account</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/deleting-my-facebook-account/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 16:16:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/deleting-my-facebook-account/</guid>
      <description>Today I reactivated my Facebook account just to be able to delete it completely. If you find Facebook useful, you should at least be aware of its potential privacy issues, and tune your privacy settings to a level that you find comfortable. Here are some links where you can find more information: 
http://www.theregister.co.uk/2010/05/14/facebook_trust_dumb/ http://www.fastcompany.com/1624745/time-to-audit-your-facebook-privacy-settings http://www.fastcompany.com/1648478/online-privacy-check-yourself-before-you-w... 
Personally, I don&#39;t find Facebook useful enough to go through the hassle. My account has been deactivated for the last couple of weeks and I haven&#39;t missed it, so now it&#39;s time to permanently delete it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hail Storm Oklahoma City</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/hail-storm-oklahoma-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 15:57:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/hail-storm-oklahoma-city/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Incredible hail storm. It gets really intense around 1:30, the pool looks like it&#39;s boiling.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Moment in Time - Interactive Feature</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-moment-in-time---interactive-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2010 12:38:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-moment-in-time---interactive-feature/</guid>
      <description>via nytimes.com  Amazing. Follow the link to get it full size.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My latest speedtest results</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-latest-speedtest-results/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 16:47:29 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-latest-speedtest-results/</guid>
      <description>My ISP recently upgraded my connection at home to 3Mbps. I&#39;m surprised it&#39;s so accurate :-)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Evolution of Privacy on Facebook and why I&#39;m dropping off</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-evolution-of-privacy-on-facebook-and-why-im-dropping-off/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 May 2010 10:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-evolution-of-privacy-on-facebook-and-why-im-dropping-off/</guid>
      <description>via mattmckeon.com  This is a very good analysis, and is why my Facebook account is currently deactivated, and probably will be deleted. Contrary to Matt, I don&#39;t find Facebook very useful. Mostly it&#39;s served me to be found by people by whom I wasn&#39;t all that interested in being found, to see relatives&#39; photos (which I can also receive through other means), to be endlessly spammed by people playing Farmville and, most usefully, to contact people whose email addresses I don&#39;t have or can&#39;t bother to remember.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cory Doctorow: Persistence Pays Parasites</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/cory-doctorow-persistence-pays-parasites/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 May 2010 10:08:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/cory-doctorow-persistence-pays-parasites/</guid>
      <description>I don’t have a solution, but at least I have a better understanding of the problem. Falling victim to a scam isn’t just a matter of not being wise to the ways of the world: it’s a matter of being caught out in a moment of distraction and of unlikely circumstance. via locusmag.com  Good lesson to stay always alert, even if you think you know better.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Zomboni</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-zomboni/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 May 2010 15:11:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-zomboni/</guid>
      <description>Behold, the Zomboni from PvZ on my iPod.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Avatar Blu-Ray DVD on LG BD370 player</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/avatar-blu-ray-dvd-on-lg-bd370-player/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2010 01:32:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/avatar-blu-ray-dvd-on-lg-bd370-player/</guid>
      <description>Just for the record, the Avatar Blu-Ray DVD plays correctly on my LG BD370 player, with the latest firmware (V7.170.00.26, upgraded from the device). I get a message saying &#34;your player may need an upgrade&#34;, then the screen goes black, but after about 45 seconds, the DVD menu appears and you can play the movie correctly.
The first time I watched it, the black screen freaked me out, I didn&#39;t wait too long, and ended up watching the movie from the regular DVD.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Starting VirtualCenter automatically when it fails to start</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/starting-virtualcenter-automatically-when-it-fails-to-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 May 2010 13:13:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/starting-virtualcenter-automatically-when-it-fails-to-start/</guid>
      <description>Create a .bat file with following script:net start MSSQL$SQLEXP_VIM
ping 127.0.0.1 -n 120 -w 1000 &amp;gt; null
net start vpxd
Note: for SQL Server substitute MSSQLSERVER in the above batch file instead of MSSQL$SQLEXP_VIM.
Set script to run on boot.
via communities.vmware.com  In one of my VirtualCenter servers, a Windows XP machine, the VirtualCenter Server service often fails to start because it tries to run before the MSSQL server is fully initialized.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Thoughts on Flash</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/thoughts-on-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Apr 2010 12:10:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/thoughts-on-flash/</guid>
      <description>Perhaps Adobe should focus more on creating great HTML5 tools for the future, and less on criticizing Apple for leaving the past behind. via apple.com  Letter from Steve Jobs about why Apple does not support Flash on their mobile devices.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>David Allen Getting Things Done | DCGTD</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/david-allen-getting-things-done--dcgtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Apr 2010 11:35:58 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/david-allen-getting-things-done--dcgtd/</guid>
      <description> via dcgtd.com  Nice brief overview from the GTD guy himself. Simple system, simple tools.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How important are the tools you use with GTD?</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-important-are-the-tools-you-use-with-gtd/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 09:24:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-important-are-the-tools-you-use-with-gtd/</guid>
      <description>via gtdtimes.com  Short video of David Allen talking about the importance of the GTD tools you choose. Conclusion: the most important thing is that you choose a tool you actually use, because the moment you stop putting your stuff in it, it will stop working.Timely for me as I rebuild my GTD toolbox and system this week.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Know your tools </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/know-your-tools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Apr 2010 02:01:36 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/know-your-tools/</guid>
      <description>I recently had to copy a very large file (&amp;gt;4GB) from a remote Windows share to my Windows 7 machine, over a very finicky connection (frequently-failing VPN over a slow Internet connection). A GUI copy didn&#39;t work because the connection dropped frequently. I tried Free Download Manager, which was the recommended tool for the download, but surprisingly, it wasn&#39;t always able to restart the download after connectivity dropped.
Then a colleague pointed me to the &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gorgeous nightscape timelapse | Bad Astronomy</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/gorgeous-nightscape-timelapse--bad-astronomy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Apr 2010 01:22:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/gorgeous-nightscape-timelapse--bad-astronomy/</guid>
      <description> via blogs.discovermagazine.com  Beautiful video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HTML5 presentation</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/html5-presentation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Apr 2010 01:29:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/html5-presentation/</guid>
      <description>HTML5*   Web Development to the next level  via apirocks.com  Really impressive presentation about HTML5, done in HTML5. Works well in Chrome.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Planes or Volcano?</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/planes-or-volcano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 14:30:14 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/planes-or-volcano/</guid>
      <description>  via informationisbeautiful.net  Keeping things in perspective. Maybe the volcano is a good thing for the environment after all.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>octopus steals my video camera and swims off with it (while it&#39;s Recording)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/octopus-steals-my-video-camera-and-swims-off-with-it-while-its-recording/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2010 13:57:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/octopus-steals-my-video-camera-and-swims-off-with-it-while-its-recording/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  Amazing footage of an octopus stealing (and finally relinquishing) a diver&#39;s camera, with everything recorded.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Army Creates Fleet of Robots On Segways! | Singularity Hub</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/army-creates-fleet-of-robots-on-segways--singularity-hub/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 14:47:10 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/army-creates-fleet-of-robots-on-segways--singularity-hub/</guid>
      <description> via singularityhub.com  What a cool use for Segways - man-sized robots able to move in many ways like humans, act unpredictably and react to other robots, humans and the environment.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet The iPad Developers - Message To Mac Customers</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/meet-the-ipad-developers---message-to-mac-customers/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Apr 2010 12:47:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/meet-the-ipad-developers---message-to-mac-customers/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  &#34;And you are gross.&#34;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting up my GTD system in Windows - links </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/setting-up-my-gtd-system-in-windows---links/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 17:54:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/setting-up-my-gtd-system-in-windows---links/</guid>
      <description>Since I started at my new job and moved to a new machine and OS, my old GTD setup has fallen by the wayside and I have found myself at a loss trying to keep track of things. I have found OneNote to be a very useful tool for keeping notes and reference material, and Outlook 2010 is actually not that bad as a task/calendar/email management tool.
 So, as a first step, here are some links I have found and which I am in the process of reading and digesting for creating my own setup:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ross sisters - Solid Potato Salad (VHS quality)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/ross-sisters---solid-potato-salad-vhs-quality/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 00:07:42 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/ross-sisters---solid-potato-salad-vhs-quality/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  AMAZING. Start watching at 1:00 if you want to skip to the good part.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Queretaro: Internet Cerca de Todos</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/queretaro-internet-cerca-de-todos/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Apr 2010 23:59:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/queretaro-internet-cerca-de-todos/</guid>
      <description> via queretaro.gob.mx  Queretaro, where I live, is abundant in free WiFi hotspots, they claim they are the Mexican city with the most coverage. In any case, it&#39;s very nice, most parks and public places or government buildings have free Internet access, and in my experience it&#39;s even not too slow.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sachin&#39;s guide to buying an iPad</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/sachins-guide-to-buying-an-ipad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 15:32:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/sachins-guide-to-buying-an-ipad/</guid>
      <description> Given all this, I predict that later this year the iPad product line will be something like:   $499, 16GB WiFi $599, 32GB 3G $699, 64GB, 3G  Bottom line: If you are on the fence about buying a 1.0 iPad, go with the cheapest model.
 via sachin.posterous.com  Interesting and useful analysis.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Installing Windows XP in Vmware ESX - &#34;Setup did not find any hard disk drives installed in your computer.&#34; | TechHead.co.uk</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-windows-xp-in-vmware-esx---setup-did-not-find-any-hard-disk-drives-installed-in-your-computer.--techhead.co.uk/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 15:20:18 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/installing-windows-xp-in-vmware-esx---setup-did-not-find-any-hard-disk-drives-installed-in-your-computer.--techhead.co.uk/</guid>
      <description>Trying to install Windows XP within VMWare ESX and getting the following error message?
&#34;Setup did not find any hard disk drives installed in your computer.&#34;
The reason for this is that the necessary hard disk controller drivers have not been installed.
 via techhead.co.uk  Useful information and links for installing XP VMs on a VMware ESX server.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tiobe Index: C back at #1</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/tiobe-index-c-back-at-#1/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 07 Apr 2010 15:16:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/tiobe-index-c-back-at-#1/</guid>
      <description>Position
Apr 2010 Position
Apr 2009 Delta in Position Programming Language Ratings
Apr 2010 Delta Apr 2009 Status  1 2  C 18.058% +2.59% A  2 1  Java 18.051% -1.29% A  3 3  C++ 9.707% -1.03% A  4 4  PHP 9.662% -0.23% A  5 5  (Visual) Basic 6.392% -2.70% A  6 7  C# 4.435% +0.38% A  7 6  Python 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Capturing multiple matches in Ruby</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/capturing-multiple-matches-in-ruby/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2010 01:03:52 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/capturing-multiple-matches-in-ruby/</guid>
      <description>To collect all regex matches in a string into an array, pass the regexp object to the string&#39;s scan() method, e.g.: myarray = mystring.scan(/regex/). Sometimes, it is easier to create a regex to match the delimiters rather than the text you are interested in. In that case, use the split() method instead, e.g.: myarray = mystring.split(/delimiter/). The split() method discards all regex matches, returning the text between the matches. The scan() method does the opposite.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expose for Windows Vista/7 [Clone] : Divide By Zero</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/expose-for-windows-vista/7-clone--divide-by-zero/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2010 15:27:56 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/expose-for-windows-vista/7-clone--divide-by-zero/</guid>
      <description> via blog.lib.umn.edu  Switcher is a nice Expose clone for Windows 7. The blog post includes some ideas for customization to make it look nicer (i.e. more Mac-like :-) than the default.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Virtual Choir: How We Did It « SoaringLeap.com</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-virtual-choir-how-we-did-it--soaringleap.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Mar 2010 12:00:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-virtual-choir-how-we-did-it--soaringleap.com/</guid>
      <description>via ericwhitacre.wordpress.com  Beautiful video of a choir that has never met in real life. Follow the link for the story (and more videos) of how it came to be.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>NASA space shuttle missions get Hollywood-style movie posters                                            - Telegraph</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/nasa-space-shuttle-missions-get-hollywood-style-movie-posters----------------------------------------------telegraph/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 01:03:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/nasa-space-shuttle-missions-get-hollywood-style-movie-posters----------------------------------------------telegraph/</guid>
      <description>  via telegraph.co.uk  Follow the link for the whole series.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>El auto de Google Maps Street View — Paola Villarreal</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/el-auto-de-google-maps-street-view--paola-villarreal/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 00:42:28 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/el-auto-de-google-maps-street-view--paola-villarreal/</guid>
      <description>  via paolavillarreal.name  Rare closeup- and inside-photos of a Google Street View car in Mexico City (follow the link for more photos)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Solving hangs in Emacs on Windows</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/solving-hangs-in-emacs-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Mar 2010 11:22:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/solving-hangs-in-emacs-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>One change I made that had a significant improvement (for me anyway) was to add the following to my .emacs file:
; try to improve slow performance on windows.(setq w32-get-true-file-attributes nil)  It seems this variable was changed to default to &#34;true&#34; relatively recently and is known to cause some slow-down problems around file access. I still get some random hangs now and then (probably due to my .emacs customisations) but it is much better now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>SolarBeat</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/solarbeat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Mar 2010 23:05:40 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/solarbeat/</guid>
      <description> via whitevinyldesign.com  Neat.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Government Agency Apologizes for Evicting British Jedi - Lowering the Bar</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/government-agency-apologizes-for-evicting-british-jedi---lowering-the-bar/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 22:06:25 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/government-agency-apologizes-for-evicting-british-jedi---lowering-the-bar/</guid>
      <description>&#34;Jedis are very welcome to shop in our stores,&#34; he said, &#34;although we would ask them to remove their hoods. via loweringthebar.net  Hilarious story, particularly the response from the Tesco representative. I&#39;d say that&#39;s the only way to deal with wackos like that - make fun of them on their own terms.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My Head is in the Cloud</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-head-is-in-the-cloud/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2010 15:27:18 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-head-is-in-the-cloud/</guid>
      <description> My head was once filled with bits and pieces of information like phone numbers, to-do lists, and addresses. I’ve ceded that responsibility to technology.
 via tweetagewasteland.com  So very true.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How’s that for a low price guarantee?</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/hows-that-for-a-low-price-guarantee/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Mar 2010 12:26:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/hows-that-for-a-low-price-guarantee/</guid>
      <description>via passiveaggressivenotes.com  Great sense of humor (follow the link for more signs from the same store). Reminds me of the signs in a Shakey&#39;s Pizza place where we used to go when I was a kid. Two I remember:&#34;We have a deal with the bank. The bank doesn&#39;t make pizza, and we don&#39;t take checks.&#34;&#34;If you would like to use your plate for your cigarette ashes, please ask the waiter to serve your pizza in the ashtray&#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shooting Stars Explained</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/shooting-stars-explained/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Mar 2010 12:27:44 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/shooting-stars-explained/</guid>
      <description>Finally an explanation. 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Suck at Facebook - The Oatmeal</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-suck-at-facebook---the-oatmeal/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 15:05:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-suck-at-facebook---the-oatmeal/</guid>
      <description>  via theoatmeal.com  I&#39;ve never been a big fan of Facebook, though I think it&#39;s OK to keep in touch with family and friends who use it (that&#39;s my main use for it these days). But these behaviors really drive me up the wall.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to make the LG BD370 region-free</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-make-the-lg-bd370-region-free/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Feb 2010 11:33:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-make-the-lg-bd370-region-free/</guid>
      <description>The instructions below apply to the LBD 370 &amp;amp; 360. via videohelp.com  How to make the LG BD370 region-free (mine came set to &#34;All regions&#34; for Blu-Ray, but not for regular DVD). For the most complete instructions, see the post by BoriMar, February 06 2010. One change: I had to burn the contents of 6000.zip to a CD for it to recognize it, putting it in the USB drive didn&#39;t work, but the down/upgrade files worked fine from the USB drive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>ShadyURL</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/shadyurl/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2010 09:42:36 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/shadyurl/</guid>
      <description>Sure, you can shorten your URLs, but that just leaves them mildly cryptic and foreboding. Use ShadyURL to make your URLs downright alarming. via wondertonic.tumblr.com  My new URL shortener of choice :-)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying out Google Buzz &#43; Posterous</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/trying-out-google-buzz---posterous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 16:56:29 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/trying-out-google-buzz---posterous/</guid>
      <description>Posterous truly is the ideal content-generation platform. From here, I can feed every other site I use!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Must-Have Windows Software (or Windows Programs that I use) - good coders code, great reuse</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/must-have-windows-software-or-windows-programs-that-i-use---good-coders-code-great-reuse/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 10:12:38 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/must-have-windows-software-or-windows-programs-that-i-use---good-coders-code-great-reuse/</guid>
      <description>I am not just a Linux enthusiast, I also happen to use Windows quite often. In fact, Windows is my primary desktop from which I connect to all the other boxes and do my work on. During the years of Windows usage, I have accumulated a list of must-have Windows programs that I wouldn’t be able to work without. Some of them are commercial, some are freeware, but that doesn’t matter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rugged software</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/rugged-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2010 10:03:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/rugged-software/</guid>
      <description>I am rugged - and more importantly, my code is rugged.  I recognize that software has become a foundation of our modern world.
I recognize the awesome responsibility that comes with this foundational role.
I recognize that my code will be used in ways I cannot anticipate, in ways it was not designed, and for longer than it was ever intended.
I recognize that my code will be attacked by talented and persistent adversaries who threaten our physical, economic, and national security.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fraser Speirs - Future Shock</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fraser-speirs---futureshock/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2010 22:15:48 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fraser-speirs---futureshock/</guid>
      <description>Secretly, I suspect, we technologists quite liked the idea that Normals would be dependent on us for our technological shamanism. Those incantations that only we can perform to heal their computers, those oracular proclamations that we make over the future and the blessings we bestow on purchasing choices. via speirs.org  Very interesting post about the negative reactions to the Apple iPad.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s first Super Bowl ad. Awesome. Google search influences so many decisions we make in life - Sachin&#39;s web archive</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/googles-first-super-bowl-ad.-awesome.-google-search-influences-so-many-decisions-we-make-in-life---sachins-web-archive/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2010 14:45:53 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/googles-first-super-bowl-ad.-awesome.-google-search-influences-so-many-decisions-we-make-in-life---sachins-web-archive/</guid>
      <description>via sachinlet.posterous.com  Really cute ad.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Procrastination 	</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/procrastination/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2010 23:42:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/procrastination/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  So true.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The &#39;Israelification&#39; of airports: High security, little bother - thestar.com</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-israelification-of-airports-high-security-little-bother---thestar.com/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Jan 2010 14:13:16 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-israelification-of-airports-high-security-little-bother---thestar.com/</guid>
      <description>Israelis, unlike Canadians and Americans, don&#39;t take s--- from anybody. When the security agency in Israel (the ISA) started to tighten security and we had to wait in line for — not for hours — but 30 or 40 minutes, all hell broke loose here. We said, &#39;We&#39;re not going to do this. You&#39;re going to find a way that will take care of security without touching the efficiency of the airport.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I like the twittelator splash screen. Reminds me of the original Alien posters. </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/i-like-the-twittelator-splash-screen.-reminds-me-of-the-original-alien-posters./</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2010 22:11:26 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/i-like-the-twittelator-splash-screen.-reminds-me-of-the-original-alien-posters./</guid>
      <description>
 via twittelator  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trying out post.ly. I don&#39;t yet fully get what the difference is with just posting to my posterous blog.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/trying-out-post.ly.-i-dont-yet-fully-get-what-the-difference-is-with-just-posting-to-my-posterous-blog./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2010 10:04:55 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/trying-out-post.ly.-i-dont-yet-fully-get-what-the-difference-is-with-just-posting-to-my-posterous-blog./</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatically cc myself in Outlook</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/automatically-cc-myself-in-outlook/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2010 12:18:51 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/automatically-cc-myself-in-outlook/</guid>
      <description>I like to Cc myself in all emails I sent. This has a few advantages over the automatically-stored copies in the “Sent” folder that most email clients create, the most important being that the handling of “Sent” varies significantly from client to client – some store it on the server, some store it locally, some erase it after a while, etc., whereas having a copy in my Inbox means it’s readily accessible and in the same place as other messages from the same thread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Keep being AWESOME!</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/keep-being-awesome/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 22:12:13 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/keep-being-awesome/</guid>
      <description> via epicwinftw.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sumerians Look On In Confusion As God Creates World | The Onion</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/sumerians-look-on-in-confusion-as-god-creates-world--the-onion/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Dec 2009 00:08:39 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/sumerians-look-on-in-confusion-as-god-creates-world--the-onion/</guid>
      <description>A booming voice is saying, &#39;Let there be light,&#39; but there is already light. It is saying, &#39;Let the earth bring forth grass,&#39; but I am already standing on grass. via theonion.com  Hilarious!
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Known Universe Scientifically Rendered For All to See</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-known-universe-scientifically-rendered-for-all-to-see/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Dec 2009 23:59:47 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-known-universe-scientifically-rendered-for-all-to-see/</guid>
      <description> via amnh.org  Amazing video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nieve en Coyoacan</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/nieve-en-coyoacan/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Dec 2009 23:16:03 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/nieve-en-coyoacan/</guid>
      <description>It&#39;s an ad, but it&#39;s very nicely done.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musical DNA</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/musical-dna/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Dec 2009 23:48:00 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/musical-dna/</guid>
      <description> via musicaldna.com and @jensmccabe  Very interesting music visualization technique.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israeli Security Opens Fire on a MacBook. Thrice. - Tom&#39;s Hardware</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/israeli-security-opens-fire-on-a-macbook.-thrice.---toms-hardware/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 16:15:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/israeli-security-opens-fire-on-a-macbook.-thrice.---toms-hardware/</guid>
      <description> via tomshardware.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One more reason I&#39;m happy to be back in Mexico</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/one-more-reason-im-happy-to-be-back-in-mexico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 13:06:34 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/one-more-reason-im-happy-to-be-back-in-mexico/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2009 in photos (part 1 of 3) - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2009-in-photos-part-1-of-3---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 01:21:42 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2009-in-photos-part-1-of-3---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  As usual, awesome photo set from TBP, showing some of the good, the bad and the superbad of 2009. Photo 39 (above) is absolutely heartbreaking. &#34;Why isn&#39;t dad reaching back to me?&#34;
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Change blindness experiment</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/change-blindness-experiment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Dec 2009 00:54:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/change-blindness-experiment/</guid>
      <description> via boingboing.net  Incredible how little attention we pay to things and people around us.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My new business card</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-new-business-card/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Dec 2009 14:14:32 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-new-business-card/</guid>
      <description>    Just arrived!

 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Passenger</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-passenger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Dec 2009 00:01:15 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-passenger/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  The Passenger.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CopperExport development paused </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/copperexport-development-paused/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2009 06:44:02 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/copperexport-development-paused/</guid>
      <description>I want to post a short update aimed at users of my iPhoto plugin CopperExport. I have received multiple reports of it failing in recent updates of Snow Leopard, and I have also verified personally that it does not work properly in iPhoto&#39;09.
Unfortunately, since the big move, I find myself without easy access to a Mac for development (I had a Mac at my previous job, and I use Windows at my new job), which pretty much makes fixing these bugs impossible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Geographic&#39;s International Photography Contest 2009 - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/national-geographics-international-photography-contest-2009---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2009 00:59:31 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/national-geographics-international-photography-contest-2009---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  Amazing photos from TBP. I was at the Iguazu Falls many years ago, and it&#39;s a majestic and breathtaking place.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After the move</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/after-the-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2009 23:29:08 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/after-the-move/</guid>
      <description>So, three weeks after our move back to Mexico, things are going well. We battled some illnesses in the beginning (we got a pretty bad cold), but we are all but recovered now, and we&#39;ve been extremely busy. We are in the process of finding a place to live, moving from Mexico City (where we arrived, and where my new job started) to Queretaro (where my permanent job will be), buying a car, finding a school, and many other &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Server-less does not mean service-less</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/server-less-does-not-mean-service-less/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2009 23:01:22 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/server-less-does-not-mean-service-less/</guid>
      <description>For a few weeks now, all of mine and my family&#39;s online presence and services have been running exclusively using free services. Before, we shared a rented server with some friends, and that server hosted all the services provided by all of our domains: zzamboni.org, sorianoramirez.org, newmoms.ch and virtsecurity.org. 
Now, with our moving to a different country and all that, we decided to eliminate the need to rent a server, and even reduce costs in the process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Character interactions charts (xkcd)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/character-interactions-charts-xkcd/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Nov 2009 21:27:20 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/character-interactions-charts-xkcd/</guid>
      <description>  via xkcd.com  Amazing. The amount of work that went into these (particularly for LOTR) is staggering.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Walking to work</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/walking-to-work/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Oct 2009 03:25:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/walking-to-work/</guid>
      <description>
   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Packed and ready to go</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/packed-and-ready-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2009 07:57:06 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/packed-and-ready-to-go/</guid>
      <description>This was the scene last night in our cellar. It was all gone this morning.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Drives On What Side?   	</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/drives-on-what-side/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 12 Oct 2009 06:38:04 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/drives-on-what-side/</guid>
      <description>via reflectionof.me  Interesting map. I didn&#39;t know Argentina used to drive on the left side (until 1945, according to Wikipedia: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Right-_and_left-hand_traffic#Argentina )
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>xkcd - A Webcomic - Scary</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/xkcd---a-webcomic---scary/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Oct 2009 05:44:08 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/xkcd---a-webcomic---scary/</guid>
      <description>  via xkcd.com  Scary indeed. From the alt text &#34;I&#39;m teaching every 8-year-old relative to say this, and every 14-year-old to do the same thing with Toy Story. Also, Pokemon hit the US over a decade ago and kids born after Aladdin came out will turn 18 next year.&#34;I feel old.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terminator - How It Should End</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/terminator---how-it-should-end/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 06:07:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/terminator---how-it-should-end/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tango - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/tango---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2009 03:18:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/tango---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  Beautiful set of photos from TBP
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gyrowheel by Gyrobike interbike 2009</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/gyrowheel-by-gyrobike-interbike-2009/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 05 Oct 2009 15:45:46 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/gyrowheel-by-gyrobike-interbike-2009/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  How very cool - using a gyroscope as an alternative to training wheels.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barack Obama&#39;s amazingly consistent smile </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/barack-obamas-amazingly-consistent-smile/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 08:01:27 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/barack-obamas-amazingly-consistent-smile/</guid>
      <description> via vimeo.com  20-second clip of Obama photos with 130 visiting dignitaries at the UN meeting. I wonder how much time he spent practicing that smile?
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Crash test: 1959 Bel Air vs 2009 Malibu</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/crash-test-1959-bel-air-vs-2009-malibu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 06:26:07 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/crash-test-1959-bel-air-vs-2009-malibu/</guid>
      <description>via iihs.org  &#34;[They] don&#39;t build cars like they used to. They build them better.&#34;The difference in the crash results is astonishing (look at both the photos and the video).
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Carl Sagan - &#39;A Glorious Dawn&#39;  ft Stephen Hawking (Cosmos Remixed)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/carl-sagan---a-glorious-dawn--ft-stephen-hawking-cosmos-remixed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 28 Sep 2009 06:03:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/carl-sagan---a-glorious-dawn--ft-stephen-hawking-cosmos-remixed/</guid>
      <description> via youtube.com  
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A fresh start</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-fresh-start/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2009 17:50:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/a-fresh-start/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Ideally Blue, my new blog about life, technology and whatever else comes to my mind.

As part of the process to leave Switzerland, my wife and I decided to stop using our own self-managed server (which we have used for over two years, shared with some good friends) and move everything to &#34;the cloud&#34;, using hosted services. This includes mainly email, which we moved to Google Apps, and several web sites and blogs, which turned out to be the complicated bit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brau-huus cheeseburger</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/brau-huus-cheeseburger/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 07:55:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/brau-huus-cheeseburger/</guid>
      <description>--Diego</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Waedenswiler beer.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/waedenswiler-beer./</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Sep 2009 05:01:15 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/waedenswiler-beer./</guid>
      <description>One of the things I will miss from ch --Diego</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Webcycle « Tom Scott</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-webcycle--tom-scott/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2009 07:10:22 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/the-webcycle--tom-scott/</guid>
      <description>via tomscott.com  The solution to geek fitness problems?
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Useful Usability Findings and Guidelines «  Smashing Magazine</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/10-useful-usability-findings-and-guidelines---smashing-magazine/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 06:45:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/10-useful-usability-findings-and-guidelines---smashing-magazine/</guid>
      <description>Everyone would agree that usability is an important aspect of Web design. Whether you’re working on a portfolio website, online store or Web app, making your pages easy and enjoyable for your visitors to use is key. Many studies have been done over the years on various aspects of Web and interface design, and the findings are valuable in helping us improve our work. Here are 10 useful usability findings and guidelines that may help you improve the user experience on your websites.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Windows 7 Party</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/windows-7-party/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 03:11:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/windows-7-party/</guid>
      <description>via cabel.name  Awesome edit.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>30 Bad Practices of Web Designers</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/30-bad-practices-of-web-designers/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 02:57:40 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/30-bad-practices-of-web-designers/</guid>
      <description>Every once in a while you will come across a page that just doesn’t seem ‘right’. There are three elements of a website that can be harmed by bad practice:
 The website lacks something in its design. The content is written badly. The search engines don’t like something about the site.  Considering the three points above, this article will explains the do’s and dont’s of certain design habits.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge dust storm in Sidney</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/huge-dust-storm-in-sidney/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Sep 2009 00:59:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/huge-dust-storm-in-sidney/</guid>
      <description>  via dailymail.co.uk  Unreal images.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fix MacFusion on Snow Leopard | Racker Hacker</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fix-macfusion-on-snow-leopard--racker-hacker/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 23 Sep 2009 07:20:17 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fix-macfusion-on-snow-leopard--racker-hacker/</guid>
      <description>First off, credit for this fix goes to Geoff Watts from his two tweets.
If you’re using Snow Leopard, you’ll find that the current version of MacFusion refuses to complete a connection to a remote server. You can fix this in two steps:
First, quit MacFusion.
Second, open System Preferences and then open the MacFUSE pane. Check the “Show Beta Versions” box and click “Check For Updates”. Go ahead and update MacFUSE.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>STS-128: Burritos in Space</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/sts-128-burritos-in-space/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2009 01:42:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/sts-128-burritos-in-space/</guid>
      <description> via space.com  Must be trickier than it looks :-)
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>At the Tufi fest in Adliswil</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/at-the-tufi-fest-in-adliswil/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2009 08:26:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/at-the-tufi-fest-in-adliswil/</guid>
      <description>Also, testing to posterous from my phone. --Diego</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Going home</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/going-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Sep 2009 18:09:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/going-home/</guid>
      <description>Thirteen years ago, I left Mexico to study a Ph.D. in the U.S. In the meantime, apart from doing that, I got married, we moved to Switzerland, and we formed a beautiful family. I have learned so many things, I have changed in so many ways. In the words of my advisor, during one of our very early email exchanges, before I went to Purdue:
It isn&#39;t so much a leaving as a beginning of something else.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Send to Posterous directly from Google Reader</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/send-to-posterous-directly-from-google-reader/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Aug 2009 00:52:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/send-to-posterous-directly-from-google-reader/</guid>
      <description>We&#39;re big fans of Google Reader. It&#39;s one of the easiest ways to view everyone&#39;s stuff fast. Yesterday, Google Reader added a new Send To feature that lets you post to your favorite places right from Google Reader while you&#39;re looking at stuff.
By popular demand, now you can use this new Send To feature with Posterous. Go to Settings &amp;gt; Send To in Google Reader and under &#34;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hiroshima, 64 years ago - The Big Picture</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/hiroshima-64-years-ago---the-big-picture/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2009 04:34:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/hiroshima-64-years-ago---the-big-picture/</guid>
      <description>  via boston.com  Powerful set of photos. Never again.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untitled 2</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jul 2009 13:18:34 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-2/</guid>
      <description>
  via tweetie </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kuroshio Sea - 2nd largest aquarium tank in the world - (song is Please don&#39;t go by Barcelona) </title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/kuroshio-sea---2nd-largest-aquarium-tank-in-the-world---song-is-please-dont-go-by-barcelona/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2009 15:59:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/kuroshio-sea---2nd-largest-aquarium-tank-in-the-world---song-is-please-dont-go-by-barcelona/</guid>
      <description> via vimeo.com  Beautiful video.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Toothpaste For Dinner - Antidextrous</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/toothpaste-for-dinner---antidextrous/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2009 05:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/toothpaste-for-dinner---antidextrous/</guid>
      <description>  via toothpastefordinner.com  I must be antidextrous too.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Posterous keeps getting better</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/posterous-keeps-getting-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2009 05:56:59 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/posterous-keeps-getting-better/</guid>
      <description>Posterous now supports even GitHub Gists - they keep adding support for more and more different sites, both for embedding and for auto-posting. I can&#39;t wait to get my iPhone, to use it more and more effectively everywhere. 
http://blog.posterous.com/posterous-now-supports-traileraddict-embeds-a </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mate</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/mate/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jun 2009 08:19:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/mate/</guid>
      <description>
  via tweetie </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Untitled 1</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 May 2009 04:28:23 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/untitled-1/</guid>
      <description>
  via tweetie </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to trick an RHEL5 client install to use server RPMs</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-trick-an-rhel5-client-install-to-use-server-rpms/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Oct 2008 04:09:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/how-to-trick-an-rhel5-client-install-to-use-server-rpms/</guid>
      <description>For one of my projects at work, I am using a test install of RHEL5 in &#34;workstation&#34; mode, but I needed to install some packages that are only available in the &#34;server&#34; package list. To temporarily make yum search the server repositories, just change the following line in /etc/sysconfig/rhn/up2date: 
versionOverride=5Server 
(normally the value is empty). </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy video conversion in Mac OS X</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/easy-video-conversion-in-mac-os-x/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Oct 2008 16:15:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/easy-video-conversion-in-mac-os-x/</guid>
      <description>After a lot of searching (and trying iMovie) for how to convert a video file to flash (.flv) format, I found ffmpegX, a nice tool that does all the hard work, invoking other tools in the backend as needed. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Synchronizing 1Password data between two local accounts (howto)</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/synchronizing-1password-data-between-two-local-accounts-howto/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Sep 2008 05:06:09 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/synchronizing-1password-data-between-two-local-accounts-howto/</guid>
      <description>I am a big fan of the incredibly useful 1Password. The latest beta release (2.8.3.BETA-11) introduces a new keychain format that, among other things, allows 1Password to detect changes made to the file by other programs and reload the changes on the fly. I am using this now to keep my 1P data synchronized between my work and personal accounts on my machine. Here&#39;s what I did:
 In my work account (dza), switch to the AgileKeyChain format by following the instructions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Adding growl notification to Raymond Page&#39;s bash prompt code</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/adding-growl-notification-to-raymond-pages-bash-prompt-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 16:05:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/adding-growl-notification-to-raymond-pages-bash-prompt-code/</guid>
      <description>Update (2008/09/10): Giles Orr kindly pointed out that he is not the author of the bash prompt package I use, I have updated to give proper credit to the author, Raymond Page.
For some time I have used Raymond Page&#39;s bash prompt code (heavily based on the work by Giles Orr in the Bash Prompt HOWTO, you can get it at http://gentoo-wiki.com/TIP_Prompt_Magic or http://code.google.com/p/homenix/source/browse/, you need to get .prompt, .prompt_functions and .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Updated script for defining a new wallet item in 1Password</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/updated-script-for-defining-a-new-wallet-item-in-1password/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Sep 2008 08:53:35 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/updated-script-for-defining-a-new-wallet-item-in-1password/</guid>
      <description>If you have been using my method for defining new wallet items in 1Password, you may have noticed that in recent versions the display of those new items has been broken. I have updated the instructions and the script to work with the recent changes, you can get it from the same page. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fixing Mail.app&#39;s recent mail addresses problem</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/fixing-mail.apps-recent-mail-addresses-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2008 07:47:52 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/fixing-mail.apps-recent-mail-addresses-problem/</guid>
      <description>I had noticed for a while that somehow my Mail.app&#39;s &#34;recent mail addresses&#34; list was not updating (I never seemed to get any of my recently used addresses in Quicksilver). Today I noticed the following error message in /var/log/system.log: 
Mail[365]: AddressBook failed to save: Error Domain=NSCocoaErrorDomain Code=259 UserInfo=0x10c9a810 &#34;The file MailRecents-v4.abcdmr could not be opened because it is not in the right format.&#34; ({\n NSFilePath = &#34;/Users/dza/Library/Application Support/AddressBook/MailRecents-v4.abcdmr&#34;;\n NSUnderlyingException = Fatal error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Markdown support</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/markdown-support/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 09:15:21 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/markdown-support/</guid>
      <description>* Testing * if posterous * understands * markdown 
If not, it would be a nice feature to add. See [the markdown page](http://daringfireball.net/projects/markdown/) for reference. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My GTD system</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-gtd-system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2008 04:10:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/my-gtd-system/</guid>
      <description>Here&#39;s my mapping from David Allen&#39;s GTD workflow to the parts in my system that implement each component. My main electronic tools are Things (http://culturedcode.com/things/ ), Journler (http://journler.com/ ), Mail.app and iCal. My main physical tools are my HPDA, my physical tickler file, my A-Z filing cabinets and my &#34;inbox&#34; and &#34;pending&#34; boxes. 
(the workflow image is © David Allen &amp;amp; Co.) 
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Testing posterous</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/testing-posterous/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Aug 2008 05:03:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/testing-posterous/</guid>
      <description>Posterous looks quite nice, with the ability to &#34;do the right thing&#34; for different media types, and to autopost to other places. I have just set it up to autopost to my blog (http://zzamboni.org/brt/ ), we&#39;ll see if it does the right thing. 
It should also auto-post to Flickr, so here goes a test photo. 
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/vita/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/vita/</guid>
      <description>There are two versions of my CV, depending on how much detail you want to see. Both were last updated on March 26th, 2015.
 Long version: PDF. Short version: PDF.  If you have any questions or comments, or need additional information, please do not hesitate to contact me.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>