<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Obituary on zzamboni.org</title>
    <link>http://zzamboni.org/tags/obituary/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Obituary on zzamboni.org</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:36:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://zzamboni.org/tags/obituary/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dennis M. Ritchie, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-13-dennis-m-ritchie-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Oct 2011 00:36:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-13-dennis-m-ritchie-rip/</guid>
      <description>Dennis Ritchie passed away last weekend. He was one of the great minds in systems research and development, father of the C programming language, and one of the big contributors to Unix, both of which power the Mac on which I&#39;m typing this, the iPhone on my desk, the Windows machine I use at work, the servers on which this blog is hosted, and much of the infrastructure both you and I use to connect to it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Jobs, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-06-steve-jobs-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Oct 2011 00:26:24 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-06-steve-jobs-rip/</guid>
      <description>Farewell, Steve. Thank you for all you did for the computer industry, for design, for music, for telephony, and for so many other aspects of our lives. You will be missed.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Gene Schultz, R.I.P.</title>
      <link>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-03-gene-schultz-rip/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Oct 2011 23:08:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://zzamboni.org/post/2011-10-03-gene-schultz-rip/</guid>
      <description>A few days ago I learned through Spaf that Gene Schultz had had a severe accident and was hospitalized. Later we learned that the accident was apparently caused by an earlier stroke that went unrecognized. Yesterday, October 2nd, during the afternoon, Gene passed away.

I met Gene about 15 years ago while I was a grad student at Purdue. I met him initially at a couple of conferences, and later while he was visiting Purdue for some time.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>